<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2011-2015 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="parallel">
  <message>
    <!-- Please keep entries in sorted order -->
    <!--Resource entries for toolbox/distcomp/parallel-->
    <entry key="AutoDerefTransferred">An unexpected object was sent into an SPMD block</entry>
    <entry key="BadResourceSpecMinExceedsMax">Minimum value of numlabs specified ({0,number,integer}) was larger than the \nspecified maximum ({1,number,integer}).</entry>
    <entry key="BadResourceSpecification">The numlabs constraints for SPMD must be specified as zero to two \nscalar integers.</entry>
    <entry key="CombineErrorMsgAndStack">\n{0}\n\nError stack:{1}</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeConstraints">The NumWorkers argument for Composite construction must be either\na scalar or a vector of length 2.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeCtorArgs">The NumWorkers argument for Composite construction must be either\na scalar or a vector of length 2.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeCtorTwoVals">The NumWorkers argument for Composite construction must be either\na scalar or a vector of length 2.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeExistIdxOutOfBounds">An invalid indexing request was made.\nThe numeric argument to Composite.exist must be an array of integers \nbetween 1 and the length of the Composite (length {0,number,integer}).</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeExistIdxType">An invalid indexing request was made.\nThe argument to Composite.exist must either be numeric or logical.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeExistTooManyValues">An invalid indexing request was made.\nToo many values specified for exist.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeGetValue">The Composite has no value on the requested worker (worker {0,number,integer}).</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeSave">Saving Composites is not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeSetValue">An invalid index ({0,number,integer}) was supplied when trying to set \na value of an Composite.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeSubsasgnInvalid">The Composite is invalid; it may have been saved and loaded, which is not allowed, or the parallel pool has been shut down.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeSubsasgnInvalidRequest">An invalid indexing request was made.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeSubsasgnLengthMismatch">The number of values provided ({0,number,integer}) does not match the number of\nassignments to be made ({1,number,integer}).</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeSubsasgnNoDotRef">Dot invocation is not allowed for Composites, use the functional form instead.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeSubsasgnNoIdxCreate">Array creation by indexed assignment from a Composite is not allowed.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeSubsasgnOnlySimple">An invalid indexing request was made.\nComposite objects only support simple indexing.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeSubsasgnRHSCell">In Composite () assignments, the right-hand side value must be a cell.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeSubsasgnUnexpectedRequest">An unexpected indexing request was made.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeSubsasgnUnhandleSubsType">An invalid indexing request was made.\n{0} cannot be used as an index datatype.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeSubsasgnUnhandledSubscript">An invalid indexing request was made.\n{0} cannot be used as an index expression.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeSubsref">The Composite has no value on the following worker(s): {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeSubsrefInvalid">The Composite is invalid; it may have been saved and loaded, which is not allowed, or the parallel pool has been shut down.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeSubsrefInvalidRequest">An invalid indexing request was made.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeSubsrefNargout">Too many outputs ({0,number,integer}) requested for ''()'' indexing.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeSubsrefNoDotRef">Dot invocation is not allowed for Composites, use the functional form instead.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeSubsrefOnlySimple">Composite objects only support simple subscripting.</entry>
    <entry key="CompositeSubsrefUnexpectedRequest">An unexpected Composite indexing request was made.</entry>
    <entry key="ConcatFileWithLineNum">{0} at {1}</entry>
    <entry key="ExecutionError">Error detected on workers {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="ExecutionErrorSingleWorker">Error detected on worker {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="FactoryMismatch">The remote object cannot be created because there is\na mismatch between the returned factory functions {0} and {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="IncompleteComposite">{0} requires that all input Composites exist on all workers.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidComms">An unexpected attempt was made to build an MPI communicator\nof size {0,number,integer} when the current value of numlabs is {1,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidComposite">Invalid Composite.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCompositeAccess">The Composite value cannot be accessed because \na remote operation is in progress.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCompositeNoPool">Invalid Composite (the parallel pool in use has been closed).</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidRemote">An invalid Composite or distributed array was passed to an SPMD block.\nIt might have been saved and then loaded, or the parallel pool might have been shut down.\nUse parpool to start a new parallel pool.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidRemoteComposite">Request to retrieve invalid Composite.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidResourceSelection">An unexpected attempt to build a resource set of size {0,number,integer} \nwas made.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidResourceSet">The workers you have attempted to access are no longer available.\nThis may occur if the parallel pool has been shut down.\nUse parpool to restart the parallel pool.</entry>
    <entry key="MethodNotSupported">"{0}" is not supported for Composite objects.</entry>
    <entry key="NeedCell">The second argument to {0} must be a cell array of input arguments.</entry>
    <entry key="NeedFcnHandle">The first argument to {0} must be a function handle.</entry>
    <entry key="NoInput">The data had no value on the specified worker.</entry>
    <entry key="NoRemoteCleanup">No cleanup return was received from worker {0,number,integer}. Delete pool and restart using parpool.</entry>
    <entry key="NoRemoteErrorStack">(No remote error stack)</entry>
    <entry key="NoResource">Could not create an SPMD block to match the requested size: {0}. The parallel pool size is: {1,number,integer}{2}.</entry>
    <entry key="NoSession">An unexpected attempt was made to build a remote SPMD resource set with no parallel pool.</entry>
    <entry key="PoolSessionHasClosed">The parallel pool being used by SPMD has been shut down.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteBuildError">An error occurred building remote objects on return from an SPMD block.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteCleanupErrored">An error occurred during the cleanup following remote execution.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClear">An error occurred during remote clearing: {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteInconsistency">An unexpected attempt was made to use a remote SPMD executor with\nan invalid parallel resource set.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteKeyFlush">An error was detected on worker {0,number,integer} during remote data clearing: \n{1}.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteMismatchMixture">Some of the Composites or distributed arrays passed to the SPMD block were not compatible with each other. Only Composites or distributed arrays created using the same size SPMD blocks can be passed into a single SPMD block.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteMismatchWithBlock">A Composite or distributed array was passed to an SPMD block with which it is not compatible. The Composite or distributed array was created for use with an SPMD block of size {0,number,integer}. This was sent for use with an SPMD block of size {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteObjectRetrievedFromLabs">The distributed array or Composite retrieved from the workers is unusable.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteObjectSentToLabs">The distributed array or Composite sent to the workers is unusable.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteRetrievalError">An error occurred during remote data retrieval.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteSet">An error occurred during remote data storage.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteTransfer">A distributed array or Composite was used in the body of an SPMD block without appearing directly in the body of the block. This can happen if a distributed array or Composite is stored inside a container such as a cell array or structure. Distributed arrays or Composites stored like this will be unusable inside the body of the SPMD block.{0}.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteUnpack">The Remote variable could not be found on the worker.</entry>
    <entry key="ResourceSet">An unexpected attempt was made to use an invalid Resource Set object\nThis may occur if you attempt to save and load Composite objects.</entry>
    <entry key="ResourceSetConsistency">An unexpected remote resource set was selected for remote execution.</entry>
    <entry key="ReturnableParcelConstruction">Unexpected input arguments for ReturnableParcel construction.</entry>
    <entry key="SendableParcelConstruction">Unexpected input arguments for SendableParcel construction.</entry>
    <entry key="SessionNotRunning">The parallel pool that SPMD was using has been shut down.</entry>
    <entry key="SessionNotRunningSingleWorker">The parallel pool that SPMD was using has been shut down. Reason:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="SourceCodeNotAvailable">The source code ({0}) for the SPMD block that is trying to execute on the worker could not be found.</entry>
    <entry key="SourceCodeNotAvailableOnLab">Worker {0,number,integer} unable to find file.</entry>
    <entry key="SpmdCreationError">An error occurred during setup for SPMD execution. If this problem persists, you may need to delete and start the parallel pool again using parpool.</entry>
    <entry key="SpmdNotSupportedWithThisPool">The current parallel pool does not support SPMD.</entry>
    <entry key="SpmdOutputs">An error was thrown while attempting to return SPMD \nblock outputs from the workers: {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="TrivialResourceUnexpectedGetIdx">An unexpected index was supplied to getFromLab for the trivial resource set.\nThe index was: {0,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="TrivialResourceUnexpectedKeyIdx">An unexpected index key become unreferenced for the trivial resource set.\nThe index was: {0,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="TrivialResourceUnexpectedSetIdx">An unexpected index was supplied to setOnLab for the trivial resource set.\nThe index was: {0,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="UndefinedFunctionOnWorker">An UndefinedFunction error was thrown on the workers for ''{0}''.  This may be because the file containing ''{1}'' is not accessible on the workers.  Specify the required files for this parallel pool using the command: addAttachedFiles(pool, ...).  See the documentation for parpool for more details.</entry>
    <entry key="UnexpectedReturn">A consistency error was detected on remote object return.</entry>
    <entry key="ValueStoreKeyClass">Invalid key class - expected int64, got: "{0}".</entry>
    <entry key="WaitingForBlockInterruption">An error has occurred during SPMD execution. An attempt has been made to interrupt execution on the workers. If this situation persists, it may be necessary to interrupt execution using CTRL-C and then deleting and restarting the parallel pool.\n\nThe error that occurred on worker {0,number,integer} is: \n{1}\n.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
