<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="cefclient">
    <!-- All CEF messages and strings should go in here:  -->    
    <message> 
                
        <!-- ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ -->
        <!-- Error messages ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ -->
        <!-- ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ -->
        
        <entry key="invalidWindow">            
            <!-- 
            -->               
            Webwindow is not valid. It was closed by user or the process was terminated.
        </entry>  
        
        <entry key="noDownloadInProgress">
            <!-- 
            -->
           There is no download in progress currently.
        </entry>  
        
        <entry key="useICOForWindowIcon">
            <!-- 
            -->
           Invalid icon file format. Please use .ico file.
        </entry>  
        
        
        <entry key="usePNGForWindowIcon"> 
            <!-- 
            -->   
            Invalid icon file format. Please use .png file.
        </entry>                  
       
        <entry key="invalidIconFile"> 
            <!-- 
            -->               
            You have specified a file that cannot be found or is not an image.\nSpecify a file name that is on the MATLAB path, or use a full or relative path.
        </entry>         

		<entry key="invalidMinSize"> 
            <!-- 
            -->               
            Minimum size of window can't be greater than maximum size of the window. Please use valid size. 
        </entry>     
        
        <entry key="updatePositionMaxSize">
            The size of the object is greater than the new maximum size. The size will be adjusted to the new maximum size.
        </entry>
        <entry key="updatePositionMinSize">
            The size of the object is less than the new minimum size. The size will be adjusted to the new minimum size.
        </entry>
        <entry key="positionGreaterThanMaxSize">
            The requested new size of the window is greater than the specified maximum size.
        </entry>
        <entry key="positionLessThanMinSize">
            The requested new size of the window is less than the specified minimum size.
        </entry>

		<entry key="invalidMaxSize"> 
            <!-- 
            -->               
            Maximum size of window can't be less than minimum size of the window. Please use valid size. 
        </entry>     
        
        <entry key="jserror">
            Error executing JavaScript command: \n\n\t{0}
        </entry>
        
        <entry key="jstimeout">
            Timeout while executing JavaScript command.
        </entry>

        <!-- Callbacks ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ -->
        
        <entry key="invalidCallback" note="stringDatatypeUpdate">            
            <!-- 
            -->               
            Invalid callback type. Callback value must be a character vector, a function handle, or a cell array containing character vector or function handle.     
        </entry> 
		
        <entry key="noOpenPort">
            <!-- 
            -->
           Could not find an open port to use.
        </entry> 	
        <entry key="portInUse">
            The specified debug port, {0, number,integer}, is already in use. The debug port will be disabled.
        </entry>
        <entry key="CouldNotFindNonEphemeralPort">
            <!-- 
            -->
           Could not find an ephemeral port to use.
        </entry> 		
        <entry key="launchProcess">
            Unable to start MATLABWindow process
        </entry>
        <entry key="nonresizable">
            The webwindow object is currently non-resizable. Call setResizable(obj) before changing the window's size.
        </entry>
		
        <entry key="UnsupportedOpForWindowType">            
            This feature is not supported for the window Type.     
        </entry> 	
        <entry key="ProxyWillBeIgnored">            
            Browser process is already running. Proxy settings can not be applied at this stage. Please close all the windows and retry.
        </entry> 		

    </message>
</rsccat>
