<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2011-2016 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="parallel">
  <message>
    <entry key="ArrayWithGapsNotAllowed">You cannot create a ''{0}'' array with empty elements. If empty elements are required, use a cell array instead.</entry>
    <entry key="AssociatedJobs">Associated Jobs</entry>
    <entry key="AssociatedTasks">Associated Tasks</entry>
    <entry key="AvailableMJSClusters">{0}\nThe following incompatible MJS clusters are available:\n{1}</entry>
    <entry key="BasicLinkDispFailure">Cannot use link to display object. Something might have gone wrong with the link. For alternative ways to access object properties and behaviors, see help for {0}, {1}, and {2}. </entry>
    <entry key="BatchMethodProfileSpecified">The batch method of a cluster does not accept a profile.</entry>
    <entry key="CCSSchedDetailsGettingDataForJob">Getting data for CCS JobID {0,number,integer}.\n</entry>
    <entry key="CCSSchedDetailsGettingDataForTask">Getting data for CCS JobID {0,number,integer} and TaskID {1,number,integer}.\n</entry>
    <entry key="CJSClusterBadObjectType">An unexpected object of type {0} was encountered.</entry>
    <entry key="CacheConsistencyAdd">An internal error occurred while adding an entry to the cache.</entry>
    <entry key="CacheConsistencyRemove">An internal error occurred while removing an entry from the cache.</entry>
    <entry key="CacheConsistencyRetrieve">An internal error occurred while retrieving an entry from the cache.</entry>
    <entry key="CallbackConstraint">Invalid value specified for property ''{0}''. Allowed values are function handles or cell arrays representing callbacks.</entry>
    <entry key="CannotCalculateClusterStorage">Cannot calculate the cluster storage for a mixed cluster.</entry>
    <entry key="CannotDeployWithCloud">This application is trying to connect to mathworks.com to retrieve information about your cloud clusters from MathWorks Cloud Center. This is not supported for a standalone MATLAB application.</entry>
    <entry key="CannotDeployWithMHLM">This application cannot use the cluster called "{0}" on "{1}" because the cluster's MATLAB Distributed Computing Server license is managed online. If possible, specify another cluster that uses FlexNet license management.</entry>
    <entry key="CannotLoadCorrectly">Objects of class ''{0}'' cannot be loaded correctly from MAT files.</entry>
    <entry key="CannotSaveCorrectly">Objects of class ''{0}'' cannot be saved to MAT files.</entry>
    <entry key="CannotSetLicenseInfo">Error setting license information from job.</entry>
    <entry key="CannotUseMHLMFromDeployed">Deployed applications cannot use clusters whose MATLAB Distributed Computing Server licenses are managed online. If possible, specify another cluster that uses FlexNet license management.</entry>
    <entry key="CannotUseMHLMFromWorkers">Workers whose licenses are not managed online cannot use clusters whose MATLAB Distributed Computing Server licenses are managed online. If possible, specify another cluster that uses FlexNet license management.</entry>
    <entry key="CellStrConstraint">Invalid value specified for property ''{0}''. Allowed values are cell arrays of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="CharOnVector">Cannot call char on a vector of displayable items.</entry>
    <entry key="ChooseMDCSLicenseNotSupported">You have more than one MATLAB Distributed Computing Server license available and license selection is not supported in this environment.  You can choose the license by setting the cluster LicenseNumber property to one of your available licenses.  Valid MATLAB Distributed Computing Server license numbers:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="ClassConstraint">Invalid value specified for property ''{0}''. Values must be of class ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="CloudInvalidMessageFrequency">The message frequency ''{0}'' is invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="CloudInvalidShutdownAt">Cannot set shutdown time in the past.</entry>
    <entry key="CloudInvalidShutdownAtFuture">The shutdown time is too far in the future.</entry>
    <entry key="CloudInvalidTerminationPolicy">The termination policy ''{0}'' is invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="CloudShutdownNotAllowed">MATLAB Parallel Cloud does not support shutdown.</entry>
    <entry key="CloudStartNotAllowed">MATLAB Parallel Cloud does not support start.</entry>
    <entry key="CloudUserIdRequired">Your MathWorks account profile must have a User ID associated with it to use MATLAB Parallel Cloud. Visit www.mathworks.com/mwaccount/profiles/edit to add a User ID to your account profile.</entry>
    <entry key="CloudWaitingToStart">Waiting for MATLAB Parallel Cloud to start (this may take several minutes)...</entry>
    <entry key="Cluster" translate="false">Cluster</entry>
    <entry key="ClusterLogDirNotExist">''{0}'' does not exist. Provide an existing path to getClusterLogs.</entry>
    <entry key="ClusterLogDirNotWritable">You don''t have access to write to ''{0}''. Provide a writable path to getClusterLogs.</entry>
    <entry key="ClusterRequiresWebLicensing">This cluster requires that your MathWorks account is associated with a MATLAB Distributed Computing Server license managed online.</entry>
    <entry key="ComputerTypeMismatch">Worker computer type is {0}, but MATLAB computer type is {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="ConstructorArgInvalid">An unexpected problem was encountered applying constructor argument ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="CouldNotCreateTempDir">Could not create a temporary directory for the attached file archive.</entry>
    <entry key="CouldNotOpenFile">Could not open file "{0}", the error returned was: {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="CouldNotRemoveTempDir" note="{0} - the temporary directory name">Could not remove the temporary directory created for the attached file archive: ''{0}''</entry>
    <entry key="CreateJobZeroInputs">createJob using zero inputs has been removed. Use a cluster object as the first input instead.</entry>
    <entry key="CustomPropTypesRequired">Internal error: Reflection methods must be used with CustomPropTypes objects or metaclasses.</entry>
    <entry key="DataLocConvInvalidDataLocation">Expected JobStorageLocation to be a character vector or a structure with fields: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="DataLocationConstraint">Invalid value specified for property ''{0}''. Allowed values are character vectors or structs with fields ''windows'' and ''unix''.</entry>
    <entry key="DctSchedulerMessageBadFormatString">Unable to format a scheduler message. Error returned:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="DctSchedulerMessageInvalidInputs">The inputs to dctSchedulerMessage must be an integer value and a character vector.</entry>
    <entry key="DeletedObject">Deleted object</entry>
    <entry key="DepfunError" note="{0} - The list of files passed to depfun, {1} - The error message from depfun">Unable to calculate the dependencies of the files:\n{0}\nbecause:\n{1}</entry>
    <entry key="DiscoverUnknownRelease">Unknown</entry>
    <entry key="DisplayFormatCellStr">Input must be a cell array of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="DisplayInternalNameValueMismatch">An unexpected error occurred during display of a {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="DisplaySpecificItemsNotScalar">Specific item display is available only for scalar objects.</entry>
    <entry key="DisplayTooFewDimensionsToFormat">Cannot format dimensions with fewer than 2 dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="DisplayUnexpectedFormatError">Values for display that are not character vectors must be formatted.</entry>
    <entry key="DistcompEvaluateTaskTerminateMatlab">distcomp_evaluate_task has requested that MATLAB should terminate.</entry>
    <entry key="EndDiary">--- End Diary ---</entry>
    <entry key="EnterPassphraseForIdentityFile">Please enter the passphrase for identity file ''{0}'': </entry>
    <entry key="EnterPasswordForUserOnMachine">Please enter the password for user ''{0}'' on ''{1}'': </entry>
    <entry key="EnumConstraint">Value for {0} must be one of the following character vectors: {1}</entry>
    <entry key="EnumConstraintNotNamedEnumeration">Cannot get the names for enumeration of type ''{0}'' because it is not a NamedEnumeration.</entry>
    <entry key="ErrorExecutingPbsCommand">Error executing the PBS command ''{0}''. The reason given is: \n{1}</entry>
    <entry key="EvaluateTaskCommunicationFailure">MATLAB failed to communicate with the jobmanager.</entry>
    <entry key="ExitException" note="{0} - The function that was running when this error occurred">Worker exiting because of an error during {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="FailedToCancelJob">The cluster failed to cancel the job execution. The error was: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="FailedToInterpretState">Could not interpret state to wait for.</entry>
    <entry key="FailedToSaveProfile">Failed to save cluster properties to profile ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="FileDoesNotExist" note="{0} - the file name">Could not find the file or directory ''{0}''</entry>
    <entry key="FileSerializerCannotOpenFile">Unable to open file ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="FileSerializerCannotOpenStateFile">Unable to open state file.</entry>
    <entry key="FileSerializerDataTooLarge">Data too large to be saved.</entry>
    <entry key="FileSerializerNumFieldsValuesNotEqual">The number of fields and values to save must be the same.</entry>
    <entry key="FileSerializerStateFileNotStringData">State file does not contain character vector data.</entry>
    <entry key="FileStorageCannotChangeFolder">Unable to change to requested folder. Perhaps you do not have the correct access permissions.</entry>
    <entry key="FileStorageCannotCreateFile">Unable to create file ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="FileStorageCannotCreateFolder">Failed to create folder ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="FileStorageCannotOpenFile">Unable to open file.</entry>
    <entry key="FileStorageConstructorNotString">The constructor argument must be a character vector.</entry>
    <entry key="FileStorageCorruptMetadata">The storage metadata file is corrupt. Please delete all files in the JobStorageLocation and try again.</entry>
    <entry key="FileStorageEntityEndInID">The location of an entity must end in its ID - an integer greater than zero.</entry>
    <entry key="FileStorageInvalidFolder">The JobStorageLocation of a cluster must be an accessible folder on the current machine''s filesystem. The value supplied ({0}) is not a valid folder.</entry>
    <entry key="FileStorageInvalidJob">The expected job file {0} does not exist.</entry>
    <entry key="FileStorageMissingMetadata">The storage metadata file did not exist. Recreating it.</entry>
    <entry key="FileStorageNonExistentOrCorruptMetadata">The storage metadata file does not exist or is corrupt.</entry>
    <entry key="FileStorageNotCharOrStruct">A file storage''s location must be a character vector or struct with fields pc and unix.</entry>
    <entry key="FileStorageNotString">The location property of a file store must be a character vector.</entry>
    <entry key="FileStorageNotWritable">Unable to write to requested folder ''{0}''. Perhaps you do not have the correct access permissions. You will be unable to store any job and tasks here.</entry>
    <entry key="FileStorageNotWritableChangeDir">You do not have permission to write to the current storage location ''{0}''. You should change directory to somewhere where you do have write permission.</entry>
    <entry key="FileStorageUnableToReadMetadata">Unable to read the required metadata file ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="FileUtilsGetAbsoluteCannotChangeToFolder">Unable to change to folder ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="FindJobNumOutputArgs">findJob must be called with 0, 1, or 4 output arguments.</entry>
    <entry key="FullTrustDotNET">It is possible that the .NET configuration for this machine has not been modified to grant Full Trust to .NET assemblies located on a network share.  Please see the Parallel Computing Toolbox and MATLAB Distributed Computing Server installation instructions or contact your system administrator for more details on how to rectify this.</entry>
    <entry key="FunctionConstraint">Invalid value specified for property ''{0}''. Allowed are function handles or a character vector naming a function.</entry>
    <entry key="FunctionToBeRemoved">{0} has been removed. Use {1} instead.</entry>
    <entry key="GenericCancelFcnError">The user supplied {0} ({1}) threw an error. The nested error is:\n{2}</entry>
    <entry key="GenericCancelFcnReturnError">The user supplied {0} ({1}) must return a scalar logical.</entry>
    <entry key="GenericCommunicatingSubmitFcnRequired">A CommunicatingSubmitFcn is required to submit a communicating job.</entry>
    <entry key="GenericDeleteFcnError">The user supplied {0} ({1}) threw an error. The nested error is:\n{2}</entry>
    <entry key="GenericGetJobStateFcnError">The user supplied GetJobStateFcn ({0}) threw an error. The nested error is:\n{1}</entry>
    <entry key="GenericIndependentSubmitFcnRequired">An IndependentSubmitFcn is required to submit an independent job.</entry>
    <entry key="GenericInvalidStateString">The user supplied GetJobStateFcn ({0}) returned an invalid state character vector ({1}). Valid states are: {2}</entry>
    <entry key="GenericInvalidStateType">The user supplied GetJobStateFcn ({0}) must return a character vector.</entry>
    <entry key="GenericJobDirOnCluster">The job folder on the cluster is available only for clusters with a shared filesystem.</entry>
    <entry key="GenericLogLocation">The argument to getLogLocation must be either a communicating job, or a single task of an independent job.</entry>
    <entry key="GenericSubmissionFailed">Job submission failed because the user supplied {0} ({1}) errored.</entry>
    <entry key="GetAttachedFilesFolderFailed">Unexpected error trying to invoke getAttachedFilesFolder.</entry>
    <entry key="GetAttachedFilesFolderStringRequired">getAttachedFilesFolder accepts only character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="GetCurrentJobFailed">Unexpected error trying to obtain the current job.</entry>
    <entry key="GetCurrentTaskFailed">Unexpected error trying to obtain the current task.</entry>
    <entry key="GetCurrentWorkerFailed">Unexpected error trying to obtain the current worker.</entry>
    <entry key="GetDebugLogJobMustBeIndependent">When calling getDebugLog with for a task, the containing job must be an IndependentJob.</entry>
    <entry key="GetDebugLogScalarJobOrTask">getDebugLog must be invoked with either a single communicating job or a single task of an independent job.</entry>
    <entry key="GetDebugLogWrongCluster">The first argument to getDebugLog must be the cluster containing the job or task for which the log is to be retrieved.</entry>
    <entry key="GetSetBadPropAccess">The following properties cannot be set on objects of class {0}: {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="GetSetBadProps">The following properties are invalid for objects of type {0}: {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="GetSetPropNameString">Properties must be specified as character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="HostStringConstraint">Invalid value specified for property ''{0}''. The value must be a valid host name or IP address, optionally appended with a port number from 1 to 65535, in the form hostname:nnnn.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServer2008R2SOAFailedToAttachSession">Failed to attach to the SOA session.  Job {0,number,integer} will not be closed correctly.  Reason:\n{1}</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServer2008R2SOAFailedToCloseSession">Failed to close session.  Reason:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServer2008R2SOAFailedToCreateClient">Could not create the client for the SOA session.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServer2008R2SOAFailedToCreateSession">Could not create SOA session.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServer2008R2SOAFailedToCreateSessionStartInfo">Could not create SOA session start info.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServer2008R2SOAFailedToSendRequests">Could not send the requests for the SOA job.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServer2008SOAFailedToCloseSOAClient">Failed to close SOA client for job {0}.  Reason:\n{1}</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServer2008SOAUnableToLaunchSOAClient">Failed to create SOA client.  You cannot submit SOA jobs.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServer2008SOFailedToGenerateSOAInputs">Error occurred when generating the SOA job inputs.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerCancelOrDestroyJobFailed">Unable to cancel job on HPC Server. Reason given:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerCancelOrDestroyTaskFailed">Unable to cancel task on HPC Server. Reason given:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerCannotCloseSOAClient">Unable to close SOA client.  Reason:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerCannotConnect">Unable to contact an HPC scheduler on machine {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerCannotConnectCCS">Unable to contact a CCS scheduler on machine {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerCannotCreateCCS">Unable to create an instance of Microsoft.ComputeCluster.Cluster. Microsoft Compute Cluster Server may not be installed on this machine.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerCannotCreateHPCScheduler">Unable to create an instance of Microsoft.Hpc.Scheduler.Scheduler.  Microsoft HPC Server 2008 may not be installed on this machine.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerCannotDeduceClusterVersion">Unable to deduce the correct cluster version to use for a HPC Server head node on machine ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerCannotDetermineDefaultHost">No value for Host was supplied and the default HPC Server head node cannot be determined from environment variables.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerCannotFindCCSLibraries">Unable to find required libraries for Microsoft Compute Cluster Server. Microsoft Compute Cluster Server may not be installed on this machine.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerCannotFindLibraries">Unable to find required libraries for Microsoft HPC Server 2008.  Microsoft HPC Server 2008 may not be installed on this machine.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerCannotFindTask">Cannot find task in HPC Server.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerCannotRetrieveVersion">Failed to retrieve server version from scheduler.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerClientUtilitiesNotInstalled">It appears that the HPC Server client utilities are not installed on this machine.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerDefaultToNonSOAJobs">SOA Jobs are not supported on this scheduler.  Defaulting to non SOA jobs.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerDescriptionFileTooManyJobs">Job description file {0} should contain only 1 job node.  Found {1,number,integer} job nodes.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerFailedToCancelJob">Failed to cancel job on scheduler.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerFailedToCancelOnScheduler">Failed to cancel the following job(s) on scheduler:{0}</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerFailedToCreateJobFromXML">Failed to create job from xml file {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerFailedToGetEnvironmentVariables">Failed to retrieve cluster environment variable {0} from cluster with hostname {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerFailedToParseJobDescriptionFile">Failed to parse job description file.  Job Properties may be overwritten.\n\tReason: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerFailedToRetrieveNameFromCCS">Failed to retrieve name from scheduler.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerFailedToUseJobTemplate">Failed to use job template {0} on job.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerFoundTooManyHeadNodes">Found more than one cluster of type ''HPCServer'' on your network, with the following head nodes:\n{0}You can narrow the search by specifying one of these hosts as the Host argument for the HPC Server cluster constructor, either by creating a profile or by using the command:\n\tparallel.cluster.HPCServer(''Host'', &lt;desired hostname&gt;).</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerGetCannotFindTaskID">Cannot find task ID for HPC Server.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerIncompatibleSetting">ClusterOsType must be ''pc'' for HPC Server schedulers.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerIncorrectSchedulerVersion">Scheduler version {0,number,integer} is not compatible with the requested API.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerInvalidConnection">Scheduler connection must be of type Microsoft.Hpc.Scheduler.Scheduler.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerInvalidJobTemplate">{0} is not a valid job template for this scheduler.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerInvalidJobTemplateResetToDefault">{0} is not a valid job template for scheduler with name {1}.  Setting the JobTemplate to default.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerInvalidNumWorkers">The NumWorkers property for the cluster must be an integer from  1 to {0,number,integer} (total number of cores in the cluster).</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerJobDescFileNotFound">Cannot set job description file to "{0}" because the file cannot be found.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerJobTemplatesUnsupported">Job Templates are not supported for head node {0} and cluster version {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerNoHeadNodes">Found no nodes in the HeadNodes group.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerNoHeadNodesGroup">Failed to find HeadNodes node group on scheduler.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerNotConnected">Not connected to a Microsoft scheduler.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerNotConnectedToCCS">Not connected to a CCS Scheduler.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerSOAIncorrectNumberOfJobIds">Obtained the incorrect number of Job IDs.  Expected {0,number,integer}, got {1,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerSOALibrariesNotLoaded">SOA Jobs cannot be submitted from this client machine because the required libraries could not be loaded.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerSOANonEmptyTaskIds">SchedulerTaskIDs must be empty for SOA jobs.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerSOANotSupported">SOA Jobs are not supported on scheduler with name {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerSchedDetailsCommandLine">CommandLine   : {0}\n</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerSchedDetailsErrorMessage">Error Message : {0}\n</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerSchedDetailsGettingDataForJob">Getting data for HPC Server 2008 JobID {0,number,integer}.\n</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerSchedDetailsGettingDataForTask">Getting data for HPC Server 2008 JobID {0,number,integer} and TaskID {1,number,integer}.\n</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerSchedDetailsStdOut">Stdout sent   : {0}\n</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerSchedDetailsUnableToRetrieveJob">Unable to retrieve job {0,number,integer} from the scheduler.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerSchedDetailsUnableToRetrieveTask">Unable to retrieve task {0,number,integer} for job {1,number,integer} from the scheduler.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerSetFactoryValuesFromEnvironmentFailed">Failed to set the following properties that were defined in the cluster properties file ''{0}'': {1}</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerSoaDecodeBadPerformJobInitArg">Unable to convert performJobInitStr to logical.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerSoaDecodeTooManySerializedArgs">Incorrect number of arguments in serialized character vector. Expected 3, got {0,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerSoaJobsUnsupported">SOA Job Submission is not supported for head node {0} and cluster version {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerSoaJobsUnsupportedOnWorker">SOA job submission is not supported on workers.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerSoaTaskCancel">Unable to cancel tasks on SOA jobs.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerSubmitSOAFailed">Error occurred when submitting SOA job.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerTaskIdsNotSameLength">SchedulerTaskIDs and MatlabTaskIDs must be the same length for non-SOA jobs.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerUnableToCancelTask">Unable to cancel task {0,number,integer} for job {1,number,integer} because the task does not exist on the scheduler.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerUnableToConnectSOAClient">Cannot create a suitable SOA client for scheduler version {0,number,integer}. You will be unable to submit SOA jobs to the scheduler with hostname {1}. Reason:\n{2}</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerUnableToFindTask">Unable to find task {0,number,integer} for job {1,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerUnableToRetrieveJob">Unable to retrieve job {0,number,integer} from the scheduler.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerUnableToRetrieveJobNotExist">Unable to retrieve job {0,number,integer} from the scheduler because it does not exist.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerUnexpectedEnumerator">Enumerator was not positioned before the first element.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerUnknownJobStatus">{0} is an unknown job status.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerUnsupportedSchedulerVersion">{0,number,integer} is not a supported scheduler version.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerUtilsADFilterStringSearchFailed">Failed to search Active Directory using filter {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerUtilsADSearchFailed">Failed to search Active Directory for HPC Server head nodes.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerUtilsFailedToConvertValuesInPropertyFile">Failed to convert the following properties that were found in the property file:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerUtilsFailedToCreateDataLocation">Could not create JobStorageLocation ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerUtilsFailedToFindDataLocationRoot">Could not find folder ''{0}''.  Your system administrator should have created this folder.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerUtilsFailedToLoadADSearchLibraries">Failed to load the libraries required to perform an Active Directory search.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerUtilsFailedToReadPropertiesFile">Failed to read cluster properties from file {0}. \nReason: {1}</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerUtilsInvalidPropertyFile">Mismatched number of properties and values found in file ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="HPCServerUtilsUnableToContactHeadNode">Unable to contact HPC Server head node with version {0} on host ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="HPServerUtilsFailedToFindPropertiesFile">Cluster properties file ''{0}'' does not exist.</entry>
    <entry key="HPServerUtilsFailedToOpenPropertiesFile">Could not open cluster properties file ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidClusterType">An invalid cluster type was specified.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidEntitlementSelection">Invalid entry selection, choose a number from the list above.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidHostParameter">Invalid {0} specified.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidHPCServerClusterVersion">''{0}'' is not a valid HPCServer cluster version.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidJobID">Invalid Job ID {0,number,integer} Information</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidJobToDemote">The job to be demoted does not exist on this MJS.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidJobToPromote">The job to be promoted does not exist on this MJS.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidLicenseNumber">The license number provided is invalid. You must choose a license number from one of your MATLAB Distributed Computing Server licenses.\nLicense number provided:\n  {0}\nValid MATLAB Distributed Computing Server license numbers:\n{1}</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidMCRShutdownArgument">Input must be ''initialize'' or ''run''.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidOperatingSystemType">Invalid operating system type: {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidStateName">Invalid state name {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidStateToWait">It is not possible to wait for state: {0}. Valid states to wait for are: {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidTaskID">Invalid Task ID {0,number,integer} Information</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidType">An invalid parallel type ''{0}'' was specified.</entry>
    <entry key="Job" translate="false">Job</entry>
    <entry key="JobMonitorHelperMultipleClusters">Multiple clusters found when using the profile "{0}".</entry>
    <entry key="JobMonitorHelperNoCluster">Unable to find the cluster when using the profile "{0}".</entry>
    <entry key="JobMonitorHelperUnknownOption">Unknown option "{0}" provided.</entry>
    <entry key="LengthOnVector">Cannot get display value length by calling length on a vector of displayable items.</entry>
    <entry key="LicenseUnavailable">Unable to checkout a license for the Parallel Computing Toolbox.</entry>
    <entry key="LinkDispFailure">Cannot use link to display {0}. Something might have gone wrong with the link. For alternative ways to access {1} properties and behaviors, see {2}. </entry>
    <entry key="LocalCannotCancelOrDestroyJob">Cannot cancel or destroy a job that was not created by this Local cluster.</entry>
    <entry key="LocalCannotCancelOrDestroyTask">Cannot cancel or destroy a task not created by this Local cluster.</entry>
    <entry key="LocalFailedToCancelOrDestroyJob">An error occurred cancelling or destroying a job. The error was: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="LocalFailedToCancelOrDestroyTask">An error occurred while cancelling or destroying a task. The error was: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="LocalFailedToFindTaskToCancel">The Local scheduler unexpectedly failed to cancel or destroy a task.</entry>
    <entry key="LocalFailedToInterpretNumlabs">The local cluster failed to interpret the numlabs environment variable {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="LocalInvalidNumWorkers">The NumWorkers property for the cluster must be an integer from 1 to {0,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="LocalMaxAllowedWorkersExceeded">You requested a minimum of {0,number,integer} workers, but only {1,number,integer} workers are allowed with the Local cluster.</entry>
    <entry key="LocalNoDataLocation">The Local cluster could not find a suitable JobStorageLocation.</entry>
    <entry key="LocalNoSMPD">Could not launch SMPD process manager. Using fallback parallel mechanism.</entry>
    <entry key="LocalNumWorkersExceeded">You requested a minimum of {0,number,integer} workers, but the cluster''s NumWorkers property is currently set to allow a maximum of {1,number,integer} workers. To run a communicating job on more workers than this (up to a maximum of {2,number,integer} for the Local cluster), increase the value of the NumWorkers property for the cluster. The default value of NumWorkers for a Local cluster is the number of cores on the local machine.</entry>
    <entry key="LocalProfileNumWorkersExceeded">You requested a minimum of {0,number,integer} workers, but the cluster "{1}" has the NumWorkers property set to allow a maximum of {2,number,integer} workers. To run a communicating job on more workers than this (up to a maximum of {3,number,integer} for the Local cluster), increase the value of the NumWorkers property for the cluster. The default value of NumWorkers for a Local cluster is the number of cores on the local machine.</entry>
    <entry key="LocalUnexpectedTaskState">A task was unexpectedly found in state: {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="LogicalScalarConstraint">Invalid value specified for property ''{0}''. Allowed values are logical scalars.</entry>
    <entry key="LoginRequired">Failed to create the cluster due to missing login information. You must log in to use a cloud cluster.</entry>
    <entry key="LsfBjobsFailed">Error executing the LSF command ''bjobs''. The reason given is \n {0}</entry>
    <entry key="LsfBkillFailed">Unable to cancel job because the LSF script command ''bkill'' threw an error. The reason given is \n {0}</entry>
    <entry key="LsfBresumeInvocationFailed">Error executing the LSF script command ''bresume''. The reason given is \n {0}</entry>
    <entry key="LsfBsubInvocationFailed">Error executing the LSF script command ''bsub''. The reason given is \n {0}</entry>
    <entry key="LsfCancellationFailed">Unable to cancel because the cluster threw an error. Nested error: \n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="LsfCannotCancelWrongType">Unable to cancel because the job was not submitted to an LSF cluster.</entry>
    <entry key="LsfChmodWrapperFailed">An error occurred while making the file "{0}" executable. The message was: \n{1}</entry>
    <entry key="LsfCommJobHomogeneousOs">The LSF cluster cannot operate on ''mixed'' worker machines. Configure the scheduler to have OperatingSystem ''windows'' or ''unix''.</entry>
    <entry key="LsfCommJobSharedFilesystem">Communicating job execution requires a shared filesystem.</entry>
    <entry key="LsfCopyWrapperFailed">An error occurred while copying "{0}" to "{1}". The message was: \n{2}</entry>
    <entry key="LsfDuplicateTaskIds">Duplicate Task ID''s found.</entry>
    <entry key="LsfErrorRunningLsid">Error executing the LSF script command ''lsid''. The reason given is \n {0}</entry>
    <entry key="LsfFailedToParseJobId">Failed to parse LSF Job ID from output: {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="LsfInvalidDataLocation">LSF cannot copy files to the remote machine if the JobStorageLocation contains any whitespace characters. Use a JobStorageLocation that does not contain whitespace.</entry>
    <entry key="LsfInvalidState">Invalid Task order detected. Destroy the job and start again.</entry>
    <entry key="LsfLogNotPresent">The LSF output log is not present. Using ''bread'' to read any LSF messages.</entry>
    <entry key="LsfLogNotYetPresent">The LSF output log is not yet present. This is written only after job or task execution is complete. Partial output might be available using the LSF command ''bpeek "{0}"''.</entry>
    <entry key="LsfNoWrapperScript">Could not find the wrapper script file "{0}". The wrapper script must exist on the client machine prior to submission.</entry>
    <entry key="LsfUnableToFindService">Unable to proceed because lsid is not on your path. Most likely this is because your computer is not set up as a client on an LSF cluster or the LSF scripts are not on your path.</entry>
    <entry key="MHCWorkersFailedToRegister">MATLAB Parallel Cloud workers failed to start within the timeout. Workers requested: {0}, workers started: {1}</entry>
    <entry key="MHLMLicenseNotRequired">This cluster is not using the MathWorks Hosted License Manager and does not require a license number.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSAuthenticationFailed">Authentication failed.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSCannotContactClient">MJS was unable to contact the client to receive information.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSCannotContactMATLAB">MJS could not contact this MATLAB session on hostname {0} and port {1,number,integer}.  Using parallel.cluster.MJS(''Host'', ''{2}:{3,number,integer}'') to find this MJS may provide a more detailed error message.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSCannotContactMATLABNetworkDrop">MJS could not contact this MATLAB session due to a network error.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSChanged">The MJS cluster "{0}" on {1} now refers to a different cluster. This is probably because it has been restarted using the -clean flag. Please contact your cluster administrator for more information.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSCommunicationProblem">{0}</entry>
    <entry key="MJSCredentialStorageFailed">Failed to read/write credentials to the MJS database.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSExceptionTransferFail">An error that is unknown to this version of MATLAB has occurred on the server. Original message:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="MJSHeadnodeNotEnoughJavaMemory">Not enough Java memory on the head node to allocate data.  Refer to the troubleshooting section of the documentation for information on how to increase the size of the local Java memory and the memory on the head node and the workers.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSInformation">Name: {0}, Host: {1}, Release: {2}</entry>
    <entry key="MJSInternalError">The current user has not been set in this jobmanager.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSJobStorageLocation">Database on {0}</entry>
    <entry key="MJSLogRetrievalFailed">Failed to retrieve the MJS logs.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSMulticastLookupFailed">Unable to open a socket for multicast discovery. Try providing a value for ''Host''.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSMultipleFoundSpecifyHostInConstructor">Multiple MJS clusters were found.  To identify only one cluster, create a profile that specifies the Host and Name properties or specify the Host and Name inputs to parallel.cluster.MJS.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSMultipleFoundSpecifyHostInProfile">Multiple MJS clusters were found.  To identify only one cluster, specify the Host and Name properties in the ''{0}'' profile.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSNoLargeDataInvoker">Client not configured correctly.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSNotEnoughJavaMemoryToAllocate">Not enough {0} Java memory to allocate data.  Refer to the troubleshooting section of the documentation for information on how to increase the size of the local Java memory and the memory on the head node and the workers.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSNotEnoughJavaMemoryToTransfer">Not enough {0} memory to transfer data.  The maximum amount of data that can be transferred in one call is {1,number,integer} MB.  This can be changed by setting the MaxDirectMemorySize property of the JVM in this MATLAB process.  See the documentation on memory transfer limits for more details.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSNotFound">There are no MJS clusters running on the local network that are compatible with MATLAB {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSNotFoundFullySpecified">There are no MJS clusters called "{0}" running on "{1}" that are compatible with MATLAB {2}.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSNotFoundOnHost">There are no MJS clusters running on "{0}" that are compatible with MATLAB {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSNotFoundWithName">There are no MJS clusters called "{0}" running on the local network that are compatible with MATLAB {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSPausedStateNotSaved">The paused state could not be saved to the checkpoint directory. Refer to the mdce-service.log file on the head node for further details. Restarting MJS will cause jobs in the queue to begin running.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSPortUnavailable">Port unavailable.  Please use the pctconfig function if on client or mdce_def file if on worker to select a different port.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSReachableInvalidData">MJS was contactable but returned invalid data. MJS should be restarted using the -clean flag to clear out invalid stored data. Provided it is restarted with the same name and base port the existing workers will reattach to MJS.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSRunningStateNotSaved">The running state could not be saved to the checkpoint directory. Refer to the mdce-service.log file on the head node for further details. Restarting MJS will cause the queue to be paused again.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSServerError">An error occurred on the server. Original message:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="MJSTaskOrJobNotFound">The task or job could not be found.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSUnableToGetProperty">Unexpectedly failed to get a property.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSUnableToSetProperty">Unexpectedly failed to set a property.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSUnavailableEphemeralPorts">MJS has exceeded its allocation of ephemeral TCP ports.  Refer to the troubleshooting section of the MDCE documentation for information on how to increase the allocation of ephemeral TCP ports on the head node.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSUnexpectedType">An unexpected type of job was requested.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSUnhandledPropertyAccess">An unexpected request was made to access a property.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSUnhandledVariant">An unexpected request was made to access properties of an unknown object type.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSUnreachable">MJS could not be reached.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSUserAbortedOperation">Operation aborted by user.</entry>
    <entry key="MJSWorkerUnavailable">Worker could not be reached.</entry>
    <entry key="MalformedLookupURL">The ''lookupURL'' input is malformed.</entry>
    <entry key="MessageHandlerNotFunctionHandle">The input to setSchedulerMessageHandler must be a function handle.</entry>
    <entry key="MixedOsClusterMatlabRoot">You must not specify a value for ClusterMatlabRoot when the ClusterOsType is ''mixed''.</entry>
    <entry key="MpiFailToReadPortInfo">Couldn''t read port information from: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="MpiFailToWritePortInfo">Couldn''t write port information to: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="MpiexecCannotCancel">Unable to cancel job {0,number,integer} because it is not an Mpiexec job.</entry>
    <entry key="MpiexecCannotWriteLogFile">Could not write to file: {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="MpiexecFailedToExtractPid">Could not determine the mpiexec process PID from the output: {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="MpiexecFailedToKillProcess">Unable to cancel job {0,number,integer} by kill process with PID {1,number,integer}. The reason given was: {2}</entry>
    <entry key="MpiexecFailedToLaunch">The mpiexec wrapper script unexpectedly failed to launch the mpiexec process.</entry>
    <entry key="MpiexecFailedToWriteBatchFile">Could not write to temporary batch file: {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="MpiexecIndependentNotSupported">Independent jobs are not supported by the Mpiexec cluster type.</entry>
    <entry key="MpiexecLaunchFailed">The mpiexec launching script returned the following exit code: {0,number,integer}, and output: "{1}".</entry>
    <entry key="MpiexecMultipleChildProcesses">The mpiexec wrapper script unexpectedly launched multiple child processes.</entry>
    <entry key="MpiexecNoMixedWorkers">Mpiexec cluster cannot operate with "mixed" worker types.</entry>
    <entry key="MpiexecNoProcessName">Could not calculate the process name for mpiexec process {0,number,integer}</entry>
    <entry key="MpiexecRequiresSharedFilesystem">Mpiexec cluster cannot support non-shared file systems.</entry>
    <entry key="MpiexecToBeRemoved">The mpiexec cluster has been removed. See the documentation for {0} for available cluster types.</entry>
    <entry key="MpiexecUnableToCancel">Mpiexec can cancel only jobs on the host where the job was submitted ({0}).</entry>
    <entry key="MpiexecUnknownEnvironmentMethod">Unknown EnvironmentSetMethod: {0} (must be either ''-env'' or ''setenv'').</entry>
    <entry key="NamedEnumerationNameMustBeString">Names must be specified as character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="NamesValuesSameLength">The same number of names and values must be specified.</entry>
    <entry key="NoClusterStorage">The cluster is configured to use ''{0}'' workers, but the JobStorageLocation property of the cluster does not include a location for that type of worker. You can specify the JobStorageLocation as a structure by doing: \nmyCluster.JobStorageLocation = struct( ''windows'', ''\\\\machine\\unc\\path'', ''unix'', ''/equivalent/path'' ).</entry>
    <entry key="NoConcurrentJobSupport">This cluster does not support ConcurrentJob submission.</entry>
    <entry key="NoDisplayAvailable">Unable to display an object of type ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="NoLocalSubmissionsFromWorkers">Workers cannot submit jobs to a local cluster.</entry>
    <entry key="NoLogFilePresent">The output log is not yet present. This is written only after the job or task starts running.</entry>
    <entry key="NoMDCSLicense">This cluster requires that your MathWorks account is associated with a MATLAB Distributed Computing Server license that is managed online.</entry>
    <entry key="NoMDCSLicenseChosen">This cluster requires that you choose the MATLAB Distributed Computing Server license to use.</entry>
    <entry key="NoMPISupportForComputer">Computer type "{0}" does not have MPI support.</entry>
    <entry key="NoMSMPISupportForComputer">Computer type "{0}" does not have MSMPI support.</entry>
    <entry key="NoNemMPILibraryOnPlatform">The ''nem'' MPI library option is not available on this platform.</entry>
    <entry key="NoSsmMPILibraryOnMac">The ''ssm'' MPI library option is not available on MAC.</entry>
    <entry key="NonEmptyCellStrConstraint">Invalid value specified for property ''{0}''. Allowed values are cell arrays of non-empty character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="NonEmptyStrCellStrConstraint">Invalid value specified for property ''{0}''. Allowed values are non-empty character vectors or cell arrays of non-empty character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="NonEmptyStringConstraint">Invalid value specified for property ''{0}''. Allowed values are non-empty character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="NotEnoughInputsForFunction">Not enough input arguments for {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="NotEnoughOutputsForFunction">Not enough output arguments for {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="NumWorkersExceeded">You requested a minimum of {0,number,integer} workers, but the cluster''s NumWorkers property is currently set to allow a maximum of {1,number,integer} workers. To run a communicating job on more workers than this, increase the value of the NumWorkers property for the cluster.</entry>
    <entry key="NumericScalarConstraint">Invalid value specified for property ''{0}''. Allowed values are numeric scalars.</entry>
    <entry key="ObjectRootNumProxiesAndObjectsNotEqual">The number of proxies and objects must be identical.</entry>
    <entry key="PBSSkipCalculation">An internal error occurred while checking job array missing tasks.</entry>
    <entry key="PBSUnableToFindService">Error executing the PBS script command ''qsub''. The reason given is \n {0}</entry>
    <entry key="PVParserInvalidPVPair">Invalid param-value pairs specified.</entry>
    <entry key="PbsCancellationFailed">Unable to cancel because the cluster threw an error. Nested error: \n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="PbsCannotAppendToWrapper">Could not make the wrapper script writable. The qsub command line will not be appended. The reason was:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="PbsCannotCancelWrongType">Unable to cancel because the job was not submitted to a PBS cluster.</entry>
    <entry key="PbsCannotReadTemplate">Failed to read from PBS template script "{0}".</entry>
    <entry key="PbsCannotWriteScript">An error occurred writing to script: {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="PbsCannotWriteSubmissionScript">Couldn''t write the submission script "{0}".</entry>
    <entry key="PbsCommandNotOnPath">Cannot create PBS cluster object because ''{0}'' is not on your path. Most likely this is because your computer is not set up as a client on a PBS cluster or the PBS scripts are not on your path.</entry>
    <entry key="PbsCommunicatingSharedFilesystem">PBS clusters require HasSharedFilesystem to be true for communicating job submission.</entry>
    <entry key="PbsCouldNotFindEnvLine">Could not find an environment directive in submission script {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="PbsCouldNotParseQsubOutput">Failed to parse the job identifier from the qsub output: "{0}".</entry>
    <entry key="PbsCouldNotReadFromScript">An error occurred reading from submission script {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="PbsDefaultServer">Could not interpret default server name from the output of ''qstat -fB''. Output was: \n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="PbsErrorCopyingWrapper">An error occurred while copying "{0}" to "{1}". The message was: \n{2}</entry>
    <entry key="PbsFailedToParseQstat">Could not interpret job state from the output of qstat -f.\nqstat returned:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="PbsJobArrayInconsistency">Internal error: could not calculate array index for task ID {0,number,integer} (Skip: {1}).</entry>
    <entry key="PbsJobArrayInvalidTaskIndex">Internal error: invalid task index.</entry>
    <entry key="PbsNoResourceTemplate">Please specify a ResourceTemplate for the PBS cluster, using the syntax "^N^" to represent the number of tasks.</entry>
    <entry key="PbsNoWrapperScript">Could not find the wrapper script file "{0}". The wrapper script must exist on the client machine prior to submission.</entry>
    <entry key="PbsProJobArraysDisabled">The PBSPro scheduler is being used with PBS Pro version "{0}". The use of job arrays has been disabled.</entry>
    <entry key="PbsProVersionCompatibility">The PBSPro cluster type is being used with a possibly incompatible version of PBS. The use of job arrays has been disabled. The version of PBS detected was: "{0}".</entry>
    <entry key="PbsQdelFailed">Unable to cancel job because the PBS script command ''qdel'' threw an error. The reason given is:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="PbsQstatCallFailed">An attempt to extract information using "qstat -f" failed:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="PbsUnableToCallQalter">Error executing the PBS script command ''qalter''. The reason given is:\n{0}</entry>
    <entry key="PbsUnableToCallQsub">Error executing the PBS script command ''qsub''. The reason given is \n {0}</entry>
    <entry key="PbsUnableToQueryState">Error executing the PBS command ''{0}''. The reason given is \n {1}</entry>
    <entry key="PbsUnsupportedCluster">The PBS cluster cannot be used with ''mixed'' clusters. Choose ''windows'' or ''unix'' for OperatingSystem property value.</entry>
    <entry key="PctConfigBadApi">convenienceapi must be either 1 or 2.</entry>
    <entry key="PctConfigBadHostInetAddress">hostinetaddress must be a java.net.InetAddress value.</entry>
    <entry key="PctConfigBadMjsPollInterval">''mjspollinterval'' should be a scalar numeric value greater than {0,number,integer} seconds and less than {1,number,integer} seconds.</entry>
    <entry key="PctConfigBadPortRange">"portrange" should be a vector [minPort, maxPort] where maxPort &gt; minPort and both ports are between {0,number,integer} and {1,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="PctConfigDeprecatedProperty">Setting the "{0}" property is deprecated and will be removed in a future release. Please set the "portrange" property instead. Setting "portrange" to [{1}].</entry>
    <entry key="PctConfigHostnameAlreadySet">Ignoring request to change client session hostname to {0}. The client session is already using hostname {1}, and will continue using that hostname for the duration of this MATLAB session.</entry>
    <entry key="PctConfigInvalidPVPair">Unrecognized parameter: {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="PctConfigUsingWellKnownPortNumber">Using a port number below 1024 often requires administrative privileges. Consider using a higher port number.</entry>
    <entry key="PoolCreateProfileRunValidation">Failed to start a parallel pool. (For information in addition to the causing error, create a profile for your cluster and validate the profile in the Cluster Profile Manager.)</entry>
    <entry key="PoolRunValidation">Failed to start a parallel pool. (For information in addition to the causing error, validate the profile ''{0}'' in the Cluster Profile Manager.)</entry>
    <entry key="PortRangeConstraint">Value for {0} must be a vector [minPort, maxPort] where maxPort &gt; minPort and both ports are between {1,number,integer} and {2,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="PositiveIntScalarConstraint">Invalid value specified for property ''{0}''. Allowed values are positive integer scalars.</entry>
    <entry key="PositiveNonZeroFiniteIntScalarConstraint">Invalid value specified for property ''{0}''. Allowed values are positive finite integer scalars that are greater than 0.</entry>
    <entry key="PositiveNonZeroIntScalarConstraint">Invalid value specified for property ''{0}''. Allowed values are positive integer scalars that are greater than 0.</entry>
    <entry key="PositiveScalarConstraint">Invalid value specified for property ''{0}''. Allowed values are positive numeric scalars.</entry>
    <entry key="ProfileDeleted">The Profile property has been set to empty because the profile with name ''{0}'' no longer exists.</entry>
    <entry key="ProfileNumWorkersExceeded">You requested a minimum of {0,number,integer} workers, but the cluster "{1}" has the NumWorkers property set to allow a maximum of {2,number,integer} workers. To run a communicating job on more workers than this, increase the value of the NumWorkers property for the cluster.</entry>
    <entry key="PropSetUnexpectedMatches">An unexpected error occurred interpreting property names.</entry>
    <entry key="Properties">Properties</entry>
    <entry key="PropertyNameMustBeChar">Property names must be specified as character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="PropertyOnlySetWhilePending">The property "{0}" cannot be set after submission.</entry>
    <entry key="PropertyValueInPairs">Properties and values must be specified in pairs.</entry>
    <entry key="PropertyValuesCell">Property values must be specified as a cell array.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessAlreadyConnected">Cannot connect to {0}: already connected to {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessAmbiguousInput">{0} is an ambiguous property input to the RemoteClusterAccess constructor since it matches multiple valid property names.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessArgumentNotLogical">The value for {0} must be logical.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessArgumentNotString">The value for {0} must be a character vector.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessCannotDoLastMirroringNotSupported">Cannot do last mirror because file mirroring is not enabled. To enable file mirroring, supply a remote data location to the connect method.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessCannotGetRemoteLocationMirroringNotSupported">Cannot get remote job location because file mirroring is not enabled. To enable file mirroring, supply a remote data location to the connect method.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessCannotResumeJobAlreadyMirrored">Cannot resume mirror for job with ID {0,number,integer} because it is already being mirrored.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessCannotResumeMirroringNotSupported">Cannot resume mirror because file mirroring is not enabled. To enable file mirroring, supply a remote data location to the connect method.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessCannotStartJobAlreadyMirrored">Cannot start mirror for job with ID {0,number,integer} because it is already being mirrored.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessCannotStartMirroringNotSupported">Cannot start mirror because file mirroring is not enabled. To enable file mirroring, supply a remote data location to the connect method.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessCannotStopJobNotMirrored">Cannot stop mirror for job with ID {0,number,integer} because it is not being mirrored.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessCannotStopMirroringNotSupported">Cannot stop mirror because file mirroring is not enabled. To enable file mirroring, supply a remote data location to the connect method.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessDoLastMirrorFailed">Failed to do last mirror for job with ID {0,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessErrorDuringChore">A problem occurred in the {0}. See the causing error for more details. </entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessFailedToCancelMirror">Failed to cancel mirror for job {0,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessFailedToConnect">Could not connect to remote host {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessFailedToRemovePossiblyDelete">Failed to remove the remote files for job {0,number,integer}. You may need to delete the job files from {1} manually. Reason:\n{2}</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessFailedToRemoveRemoteFiles">Failed to remove remote files for job {0,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessFailedToRunCommand">Failed to run command "{0}" on host {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessIdentityFileAndCredentialMapSupplied">Supplying both an identity file and a parameter map is not allowed.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessIdentityFileDir">The supplied identity file ''{0}'' is a directory and not a file.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessIncorrectRemoteOS">Allowed values of remoteOS are: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessInternalError">An internal error occurred.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessInvalidCredentialMap">The value for PCTQECredentialMap must be a ParameterMap.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessInvalidInput">{0} is not a valid property input to the RemoteClusterAccess constructor.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessNoPassword">User did not enter a password.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessNonExistentIdentityFile">The supplied identity file ''{0}'' does not exist.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessNotConnected">Not connected to a remote host.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessProblemGettingPassword">Problem getting password from command line. {0}</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessResumeMirrorFailed">Failed to resume mirror for job with ID {0,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessStartMirrorFailed">Failed to start mirror for job with ID {0,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessStdErrUnreliable">Standard error from command {0} may be unreliable.</entry>
    <entry key="RemoteClusterAccessStdOutUnreliable">Standard out from command {0} may be unreliable.</entry>
    <entry key="SSLHandshakeFailed">Failed to contact the cluster "{0}" on computer "{1}". You must specify the correct certificate when constructing the cluster. Contact the cluster administrator for the correct certificate.</entry>
    <entry key="SaveAsProfileAlreadyExists">A profile with name ''{0}'' already exists.  Either delete ''{1}'' and call saveAsProfile(''{2}'') again or choose an unused profile name.  Existing profile names are:\n{3}</entry>
    <entry key="SaveAsProfileNotAllowed">Clusters of type ''{0}'' do not support saveAsProfile.</entry>
    <entry key="SaveNonExistentProjectComponent">The project component defined in profile ''{0}'' does not exist.  No project component will be created for profile ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="SaveProfileIncorrectSchedulerComponent">The cluster''s type is ''{0}'' but the ''{1}'' profile has a scheduler component with type ''{2}''.  Either delete ''{3}'' or save this cluster to a profile with a different name.</entry>
    <entry key="SaveProfileNoProfileSet">Cannot save profile because the cluster''s Profile property is empty.</entry>
    <entry key="SaveProfileNoProfileSetUseSaveAs">Cannot save profile because the cluster''s Profile property is empty.  Use saveAsProfile(&lt;desiredName&gt;) to specify the name to use for the profile.</entry>
    <entry key="SaveProfileNoSchedulerComponent">The ''{0}'' profile does not have a valid scheduler component. A new scheduler component of type ''{1}'' will be created for ''{2}''.</entry>
    <entry key="SectorLicenseError">Submitting a task from a commercial Parallel Computing Toolbox license and running on a cluster with an educational MATLAB Distributed Computing Server is disallowed by The MathWorks, Inc Software License Agreement. Please speak with the administrator of your Parallel Computing Toolbox and/or MATLAB Distributed Computing Server license(s).</entry>
    <entry key="SetCellArrayLengthConsistency">When calling set(obj, namesCell, valuesCell), namesCell and valuesCell must be the same length.</entry>
    <entry key="SetInvalidValueForProperty">Invalid value specified for property ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="SetStructNotSupported">SET does not support struct arguments.</entry>
    <entry key="SharedFoldersConstraint">Invalid value specified for property ''{0}''. Allowed values are a two-column cell array with character vectors in the first column and either character vectors or cell arrays of character vectors in the second column.</entry>
    <entry key="StartDiary">--- Start Diary ---</entry>
    <entry key="StorageAccessIOError">An IO error occurred accessing properties: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="StorageLocationOnCluster">The cluster does not have a location defined for operating system type "{0}". Define a structure for the cluster''s "JobStorageLocation" property to support different operating systems.</entry>
    <entry key="StringConstraint">Invalid value specified for property ''{0}''. Allowed values are character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="Task" translate="false">Task</entry>
    <entry key="TaskRunnerCancellation">TaskRunner cannot cancel jobs or tasks.</entry>
    <entry key="TaskRunnerSubmission">TaskRunner cannot submit jobs.</entry>
    <entry key="TooManyInputsForFunction">Too many input arguments for {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="TooManyOutputsForFunction">Too many output arguments for {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="TorqueCouldUsePbsPro">You are using the Torque cluster with PBS version ''{0}''. You might be able to use the ''parallel.cluster.PBSPro'' cluster instead.</entry>
    <entry key="TorquePcNotSupported">The Torque cluster is supported only on UNIX platforms.</entry>
    <entry key="TypeCheckerFailedFirstElementNotFunction">Failed to convert the character vector ''{0}'' to a callback function because the first element of cell array did not contain a function handle or a valid function name.</entry>
    <entry key="TypeCheckerFailedNotCell">Failed to convert the character vector ''{0}'' to a callback function because it did not evaluate to a cell array.</entry>
    <entry key="TypeCheckerFailedNotFunctionHandle">Failed to convert the character vector ''{0}'' to a callback function because it did not evaluate to a function handle.</entry>
    <entry key="TypeCheckerToCallbackFailed">Failed to convert the character vector ''{0}'' to a callback function due to the following error:\n{1}</entry>
    <entry key="TypeCheckerToCellFailed">Failed to convert the character vector ''{0}'' to a cell array callback function due to the following error:\n{1}</entry>
    <entry key="UnexpectedExitFailure" note="{0} - the text of the error message">Unexpected error: {0} - MATLAB will now exit and restart.</entry>
    <entry key="UnexpectedExitFailureNoRestart">Unexpected error whilst finishing an interactive task - MATLAB will now exit.</entry>
    <entry key="UnexpectedExitFailureTaskNoCause">Unexpected error whilst running task - MATLAB will now exit and restart.</entry>
    <entry key="UnexpectedExitFailureTaskNoRestart">Unexpected error whilst running task - MATLAB will now exit.</entry>
    <entry key="UnexpectedFailureToGetCluster">Unexpected error trying to invoke getCurrentCluster.</entry>
    <entry key="UnexpectedStorageAccessError">An unexpected error occurred accessing properties: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="UnidentifiedJavaException">An unidentified Java error occurred: {0}</entry>
    <entry key="UnknownMPILibraryOption">Unknown MPI library option: {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="UnknownNamedEnumerationNames">The following are not valid names for the {0} enumeration: {1}.</entry>
    <entry key="UnknownTimingConstraint">Could not interpret timing constraint "{0}".</entry>
    <entry key="UnknownVariantName">Unknown type: {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsupportedType">Profiles defining clusters of type ''{0}'' are not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="UsingWellKnownPortNumber">Using a port number below 1024 often requires administrative privileges. Consider using a higher port number.</entry>
    <entry key="VarEnumConstraint">Invalid value specified for property ''{0}'' ({1}). Allowed values are: {2}</entry>
    <entry key="WorkerNumberLimitsConstraint">Invalid value specified for property ''{0}''. Allowed values are either 1 or 2 numbers specifying a range for number of workers, [minWorkers, maxWorkers], where 0 &lt; minWorkers &lt;= maxWorkers. Specifying only one number sets minWorkers = maxWorkers.</entry>
    <entry key="WarningHostCorrectedToHostNameOnly">The host name ''{0}'' is invalid; automatically using ''{1}'' instead.</entry>
    <entry key="WarningHostRemoved">The host name ''{0}'' is invalid; automatically reverting to the default value.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
