<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2010-2016 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="Simulink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../../matlab/resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
    <entry key="AbsTimeNotSuppForTsDepAsyncBlk">The Model Reference block ''{0}'' is triggered by an asynchronous function-call initiator. This configuration is not supported when the referenced model ''{1}'' needs absolute time.</entry>
    <entry key="InportFCPortNotAllowAsyncRootOutportDrivenByRTB">''{0}'' cannot be driven by a Rate Transition block that has an asynchronous rate when the model has asynchronous function-call input port.</entry>
    <entry key="InportFCPortNotAllowAsyncSfcnBlk">''{0}'' is an asynchronous function call initiator. Such blocks are not allowed in a model that has an asynchronous function-call input port.</entry>
    <entry key="InportFCPortMustUseBuildInRTB">''{0}'' is not a Simulink Rate Transition block. When a model has an asynchronous function-call input port, use the Rate Transition block in Simulink library to handle rate transitions to or from an asynchronous function-call block.</entry>
    <entry key="AsyncFCSSCannotBePeriodic">''{0}'' cannot be defined to be a periodic function-call block because it has an asynchronous rate.</entry>
    <entry key="ConstSampleTimeAtAsyncInitiator">Asynchronous function-call initiator ''{0}'' specifies a constant (inf) sample time. Constant (inf) sample time is not supported for asynchronous function-call initiators in simulation. This sample time will be changed to inherited (-1). To remove this warning message, make sure this block specifies a sample time other than constant (inf). You can do this by selecting the Simulation mode if this block has a 'Mode' option.</entry>
    <entry key="AsyncSfcnInvalidDtype">Asynchronous task defined by S-function ''{0}'' specifies invalid data type for the timer associated with this asynchronous task.</entry>
    <entry key="AsyncTsPriorityMustHigherThanBaseRate">The Asynchronous Task Specification block connected to root-level Inport block ''{0}'' specifies priority {1,number, integer}, but the periodic base rate priority is {2, number, integer}. Asynchronous task must specify a priority higher than periodic base rate.</entry>
    <entry key="AsyncTIDSamePriorityAsSyncTID">The asynchronous task associated with the S-function ''{0}'', and the periodic task with sample time {1} share the same priority: {2,number,integer}. Either specify differing priorities, or set the Tasks with equal priority option in the Diagnostics page of the Configuration Parameters Dialog to "none" if tasks of equal priority can not preempt each other in the target system.</entry>
    <entry key="AsyncTriggerInActionSys">Asynchronous subsystem ''{0}'' may not be put in an action or iterator subsystem.</entry>
    <entry key="BlkFastestTsNotGCDOfInTs">Cannot determine a sample time for block ''{0}''. Either specify the sample time of this block (a suggested rate is {1}, the greatest common divisor of the input rates) or specify sample times for the blocks that drive this block''s inputs.</entry>
    <entry key="BlkInputSampleTimeMismatch">Sample time mismatch. Sample time ({0}) of signal driving input port {1,number,integer} of ''{2}'' does not match the sample time ({3}) of the block.</entry>
    <entry key="BlkWithUnsetTsInhSupLevel"><![CDATA[The model reference sample time inheritance rule for block ''{0}'' is not set and the model is sample time independent. The generated code from the block might produce incorrect results if it is referenced by a Model block. For S-functions, specify the model reference sample time inheritance rule through the ssSetModelReferenceSampleTimeInheritanceRule macro. You can suppress the diagnostic by setting <sldiag objui="configset" objparam="UnknownTsInhSupMsg">Unspecified inheritability of sample time</sldiag> to 'none'.]]></entry>
    <entry key="BlockTsNotAMultipleOfFixedStep">The sample time {0} ({1}) of ''{2}'' is not an integer multiple of the fixed step size ({3}) specified for model.</entry>
    <entry key="CompileNeededForBlockSampleTimes">An Update Diagram must be performed in order to access the ''SampleTimes'' information for the block ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="ComputedStepSizeIsTooSmall">The computed fixed step size ({0}) is {1} times smaller than all the discrete sample times in the model ''{2}''. This fixed step size has been computed based on the following specified discrete sample times:{3} and the following propagated discrete sample times:{4} in the model. You can fix this error either by switching to a variable step solver or by specifying a fixed step size such that the discrete sample times (both periods and offsets) are integer multiples of the fixed step size.</entry>
    <entry key="ComputedStepSizeMayBeTooSmall">The computed fixed step size ({0}) is {1} times smaller than some of the discrete sample times in the model ''{2}''. This fixed step size has been computed based on the following specified discrete sample times:{3} and the following propagated discrete sample times:{4} in the model. You can disable this diagnostic either by specifying a fixed step size such that the discrete sample times (both periods and offsets) are integer multiples of the fixed step size, or by setting ''Automatic solver parameter selection'' diagnostic to ''none'' in the Diagnostics tab of the configuration parameters dialog.</entry>
    <entry key="ConcurrentTasksNotSupportAsyncSfcnRTB">You cannot use the S-Function block {0} as an asynchronous rate transition block. 'Concurrent tasks' requires that you use the Simulink Rate Transition block for all rate transitions</entry>
    <entry key="ConcurrentTasksNotSupportAsyncSysRTB">You cannot use the Masked Subsystem block {0} as an asynchronous rate transition block. 'Concurrent tasks' requires that you use a Simulink Rate Transition block for all rate transitions.</entry>
    <entry key="ConstantSampleTimeDescription">Constant</entry>
    <entry key="ConstantSampleTimeDescription_Advanced">Invariant</entry>
    <entry key="ParameterSampleTimeDescription">Constant</entry>
    <entry key="InvPrmSampleTimeDescription_Advanced">Invariant</entry>
    <entry key="SampleTimeValueNA">N/A</entry>
    <entry key="SampleTimeValueInf">Inf</entry>
    <entry key="InitializationEventDescription">Initialization</entry>
    <entry key="ContinuousSTBlkHasFrames">One or more ports of block ''{0}'' are set to be frame-based even though this block has a continuous sample time. Frame-based signals should have a discrete sample time.</entry>
    <entry key="ContSTOutPortIsFrameBased">Output port {0,number,integer} of ''{1}'' is set to be frame-based even though this port has a continuous sample time. Frame-based signals should have a discrete sample time.</entry>
    <entry key="ContTsReq">''{0}'' must have a continuous sample time since there are continuous states.</entry>
    <entry key="DefaultFixedStepSizeMsg">The model ''{0}'' will use a fixed step size of ({1}) based on start and stop times.  You can disable this diagnostic by setting the ''Automatic solver parameter selection'' diagnostic to ''none'' in the Solver group on the Diagnostics pane of the Configuration Parameters dialog box.\n</entry>
    <entry key="DiscreteBecomingInf">The periodic sample time {0}, used in block ''{1}'', is too large for use in a model with a base rate of {2}. Either explicitly specify this sample time as inf, or specify a fixed step size large enough that this sample time divided by the fixed step size will not be inf within the limits of numerical precision.</entry>
    <entry key="ErrorInParamInit">Error while initializing parameters.</entry>
    <entry key="ParamUpgradeNotification">Some of the issues encountered during parameter initialization may be because this model was created in a previous release.</entry>
    <entry key="FasterTaskMustHaveHigherPriority">For synchronous tasks, faster tasks must have higher priority. Faster synchronous task whose sample time is {0} has priority {1,number,integer}. This priority is lower than the priority of slower task whose sample time is {2}. The slower task priority is: {3,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="FixedInMinorStepDescription">Fixed in Minor Step</entry>
    <entry key="FixedStepNEFundStep">Invalid setting for fixed-step size ({0}) in model ''{1}''. All sample times in your model must be an integer multiple of the fixed-step size.</entry>
    <entry key="FixedStepSizeHeuristicErr">Unable to determine a fixed step size based on the sample times in the model ''{0}'', because the model does not have any discrete sample times.  You can disable this diagnostic by explicitly specifying a fixed step size in the Solver pane of the Configuration Parameters dialog box, or setting the ''Automatic solver parameter selection'' diagnostic to ''none'' in the Solver group on the Diagnostics pane of the Configuration Parameters dialog box.</entry>
    <entry key="FixedStepSizeHeuristicWarn">Unable to determine a fixed step size based on the sample times in the model ''{0}'', because the model does not have any discrete sample times.  Picking a fixed step size of ({1}) based on simulation start and stop times.  You can disable this diagnostic by explicitly specifying a fixed step size in the Solver pane of the Configuration Parameters dialog box, or setting the ''Automatic solver parameter selection'' diagnostic to ''none'' in the Solver group on the Diagnostics pane of the Configuration Parameters dialog box.</entry>
    <entry key="FunctionalSampleTimesNotMatchSFcn">Number of functional sample times specified in block ''{0}'' does not match the number of sample times in this block. This can happen when you build an S-Function block from a variable-step model, and then use the S-Function block in a fixed-step model. You can fix this error by switching to a variable-step solver or regenerating the S-Function block with a fixed-step solver.</entry>
    <entry key="FunctionalSampleTimesNotMatchMdlRef">Number of functional sample times specified in block ''{0}'' does not match the number of sample times in this block. This can happen when you drive two different function-call inputs of a Model block with the same Asynchronous function call initiator. You can fix this error by using two different function-call generators or by using only one function-call input inside the referenced model.</entry>
    <entry key="HiddenSigspecInputSampleTimeMismatch">Sample time mismatch. Sample time ({0}) of signal at output port {1,number,integer} of ''{2}'' does not match the sample time ({3}) specified for this signal by signal object ''{4}''.  The signal object is resolved to output port {5,number,integer} of ''{6}''.  Consider changing the signal object property, or the mismatching block setting to resolve this conflict.</entry>
    <entry key="HiddenSigspecInputSampleTimeMismatchFromBus">Sample time mismatch. Sample time ({0}) of the signal at output port {1,number,integer} of ''{2}'' does not match the sample time ({3}) specified for this signal by the bus element in the bus object ''{4}''.  The bus object is resolved to the output port of ''{5}''. To eliminate this mismatch, consider changing the bus element property or the mismatching block setting.</entry>
    <entry key="HiddenSigspecOutputSampleTimeMismatch">Sample time mismatch. Sample time ({0}) of signal at input port {1,number,integer} of ''{2}'' does not match the sample time ({3}) specified for this signal by signal object ''{4}''.  The signal object is resolved to output port {5,number,integer} of ''{6}''.  Consider changing the signal object property, or the mismatching block setting to resolve this conflict.</entry>
    <entry key="HiddenSigspecOutputSampleTimeMismatchFromBus">Sample time mismatch. Sample time ({0}) of the signal at input port {1,number,integer} of ''{2}'' does not match the sample time ({3}) specified for this signal by the bus element in the bus object ''{4}''.  The bus object is resolved to the output port of ''{5}''. To eliminate this mismatch, consider changing the bus element property or the mismatching block setting.</entry>
    <entry key="IgnoringAsyncFlag">The SS_OPTION_ASYNCHRONOUS, SS_OPTION_ASYNCHRONOUS_INTERRUPT, or SS_OPTION_ASYNCHRONOUS_CUSTOM flag for S-function ''{0}'' is being ignored because the S-function does not meet all of the following criteria: number of sample times is 1, the sample time is inherited (-1), 1 output port, and all elements of the output port are configured to perform function calls.</entry>
    <entry key="IllegalRateTransSFcnBlockPortNumErr">Illegal usage of SS_OPTION_RATE_TRANSITION by S-function ''{0}'' in ''{1}''. This option can only be used by S-functions with one input and one output port.</entry>
    <entry key="IllegalRateTransSFcnBlockTsNumErr">Illegal usage of SS_OPTION_RATE_TRANSITION by S-function ''{0}'' in ''{1}''. This option can only be used by S-functions that specifies only one functional sample time.</entry>
    <entry key="IllegalRateTransSFcnBlockContTsErr"> Illegal usage of SS_OPTION_RATE_TRANSITION by S-function ''{0}'' in ''{1}''. This option can only be used by S-functions with a discrete sample time.</entry>
    <entry key="IllegalFCSSPortRateTrans">Function calls having different rates found at {0} of ''{1}''. All function calls must have the same rate; otherwise, the behavior of simulation and generated code may be unpredictable and inconsistent.</entry>
    <entry key="IllegalInsertedRtbTsGCD">Unable to automatically insert a rate transition block between output port {0,number,integer} of block ''{1}'' running at sample time {2} and input port {3,number,integer} of block ''{4}'' running at sample time {5}. To solve the rate transition between these two ports, a block with sample time {6} is required. However, the model does not currently have this sample time and it can not be introduced by an inserted block. Consider manually placing a rate transition block between these ports.</entry>
    <entry key="IllegalInsertedRtbInputTs">Unable to automatically insert a rate transition block between output port {0,number,integer} of block ''{1}'' running at sample time {2} and input port {3,number,integer} of block ''{4}'' running at sample time {5}. To solve the rate transition between these two ports, the inserted Tate Transition block need set sample time {6} on the input port. However, the model does not currently have this sample time. Consider manually placing a rate transition block between these ports.</entry> 
   <entry key="IllegalRateTransFoundAtInportAndOutport">Found rate transition at both inport and outport of block ''{0}''. This will cause less efficient code and extra data latency. Consider reassigning the sample time of the block.</entry>
    <entry key="IllegalInsertedRtbOutputTs">Unable to automatically insert a rate transition block between output port {0,number,integer} of block ''{1}'' running at sample time {2} and input port {3,number,integer} of block ''{4}'' running at sample time {5}. To solve the rate transition between these two ports, the inserted Rate Transition block need set sample time {6} on the output port. However, the model does not currently have this sample time. Consider manually placing a rate transition block between these ports.</entry>
    <entry key="IllegalRateTransAtStatePort">The sample time {0} of ''{1}'' at {2} is different from the sample time {3} of ''{4}'' at output port {5,number,integer}. A rate transition is not allowed at a state port.</entry>
    <entry key="IllegalIPortRateTrans">The sample time {0} of ''{1}'' at {2} is different from the sample time {3} of ''{4}'' at output port {5,number,integer}. Consider inserting a Rate Transition block between the two ports. Alternatively, you can control the diagnostic action for unspecified rate transitions by changing the option "Multitask (or Single task) rate transition" on the Sample Time Diagnostics pane of the Configuration Parameters dialog box.</entry>
  <entry key="IllegalIPortRateTransViewer">The sample time {0} of ''{1}'' at {2} is different from the sample time {3} of ''{4}'' at output port {5,number,integer}. The data displayed on {6} may be off by a sample period. Consider inserting a Rate Transition block between the two ports. Alternatively, you can control the diagnostic action for unspecified rate transitions by changing the option "Multitask (or Single task) rate transition" on the Sample Time Diagnostics pane of the Configuration Parameters dialog box.</entry>
    <entry key="IllegalIPortRateTransForFramedData">The sample time {0} of ''{1}'' at {2} is different from the sample time {3} of ''{4}'' at output port {5,number,integer}. You can control the diagnostic action for unspecified rate transitions by changing the option "Multitask (or Single task) rate transition" on the Sample Time Diagnostics pane of the Configuration Parameters dialog box.</entry>
    <entry key="IllegalIPortRateTransVarDimsSignal">The sample time of ''{0}'' at input port {1,number,integer} is different from the sample time of ''{2}'' at output port {3,number,integer}. Consider inserting a Rate Transition block between the two ports. Simulink does not support unspecified rate transitions for variable-size signals; therefore, you cannot control the diagnostic action for this condition.</entry>
    <entry key="IllegalIPortRateTransNoAutoInsertFromBlock"> Simulink detected an unspecified rate transition where the sample time {0} of ''{1}'' at {2} is different from the sample time {3} of ''{4}'' at output port {5,number,integer}.  However, Simulink cannot automatically insert a Rate Transition block because the connection is made using Goto and From blocks. \n Rewire the block diagram to resolve the unspecified rate transition. Alternatively, you can control the diagnostic action for unspecified rate transitions by changing the option "Multitask (or Single task) rate transition" on the Sample Time Diagnostics pane of the Configuration Parameters dialog box. </entry>
    <entry key="IllegalRateTransAtMergeBlk">The sample time {0} of the Merge block ''{1}'' at {2} is different from the sample time {3} of its source, ''{4}'', at output port {5,number,integer}. You can address this unspecified rate transition one of three ways: \n - Make the two sample times equal; \n - Insert a Rate Transition block and a Signal Conversion block between ''{6}'' and the Merge block;\n -  Changing the diagnostic option "Multitask (or Single task) rate transition" on the Sample Time Diagnostics pane of the Configuration Parameters dialog box.</entry>
    <entry key="IllegalRateTransBlkInRightClickBuild">The subsystem right-click build resulted in an improperly configured rate transition block, {0}. Investigate this issue in the original model by verifying: \n - The original model uses a fixed-step solver; \n - The Sample Time parameters of the Inport and Outport blocks in the subsystem are all set to -1; \n - The subsystem input signals do not have a constant sample time.</entry>
    <entry key="IllegalRateTransInRightClickBuild">The subsystem right-click build resulted in an unspecified rate transition between ({0}) and ({1}). Investigate this issue in the original model, by verifying: \n - The original model uses a fixed-step solver; \n - The Sample Time parameters of the Inport and Outport blocks in the subsystem are all set to -1; \n - The subsystem input signals do not have a constant sample time.</entry>
    <entry key="IllegalRateTransDelay">The configuration of the Delay ''{0}'' is incorrect for handling a rate transition. The sample time {1} of its destination is not present on any blocks in the system containing the Delay block. Consider using the Rate Transition block to handle the data transfer between rates.</entry>
    <entry key="IllegalRateTransUnitDelay">The configuration of the Unit Delay ''{0}'' is incorrect for handling a rate transition. The sample time {1} of its destination is not present on any blocks in the system containing the Unit Delay block. Consider using the Rate Transition block to handle the data transfer between rates.</entry>
    <entry key="IllegalSampleTimeRateTransUnitDelay">The sample time {0} is too small for the Unit Delay ''{1}'' to handle a rate transition. Specify a value higher than 1e10 or choose 0 for continuous rate transition.</entry>
    <entry key="IllegalRateTransZOH">The configuration of the Zero Order Hold ''{0}'' is incorrect for handling a rate transition. The sample time {1} of its source is not present on any blocks in the system containing the Zero Order Hold block. Consider using the Rate Transition block to handle the data transfer between rates. </entry>
    <entry key="IllegalUnitDelayRateTrans">The configuration of the Unit Delay ''{0}'' is incorrect for handling a rate transition. Consider using the Rate Transition block to handle the data transfer between rates. Alternatively, you can control the diagnostic action for unspecified rate transitions by changing the option "Multitask (or Single task) rate transition" on the Sample Time Diagnostics pane of the Configuration Parameters dialog box.</entry>
    <entry key="IllegalRateTrans">The configuration of the block ''{0}'' is incorrect for handling a rate transition. Consider using the Rate Transition block to handle the data transfer between rates.</entry>
    <entry key="IllegalZOHRateTrans">The configuration of the Zero Order Hold ''{0}'' is incorrect for handling a rate transition. Consider using the Rate Transition block to handle the data transfer between rates.  Alternatively, you can control the diagnostic action for unspecified rate transitions by changing the option "Multitask (or Single task) rate transition" on the Sample Time Diagnostics pane of the Configuration Parameters dialog box.</entry>
    <entry key="InconsistentPortBasedTs">Inconsistent sample times. Sample time ({0}) of signal driving input port {1,number,integer} of ''{2}'' differs from the expected sample time ({3}) at this input port.</entry>
    <entry key="InconsistentBlockBasedTs">Inconsistent sample times. Sample time ({0}) of ''{1}'' is slower than sample time ({2}) at input port {3,number,integer}. This is likely because there is a loop of blocks, containing ''{4}'' that do not specify sample time (all are inherited (-1)). Either specify the sample time of this
block or specify sample times for the blocks that drive this block''s inputs.</entry>
    <entry key="InconsistentAsyncTimeSource">The function-call block ''{0}'' is triggered by asynchronous S-functions specifying conflicting time sources: ''{1}'' specifies ''{2}'', while ''{3}'' specifies ''{4}''.</entry>
    <entry key="InconsistentAsyncPriority">The block ''{0}'' is invoked by asynchronous S-functions specifying conflicting priorities: ''{1}'' specifies {2,number,integer}, while ''{3}'' specifies {4,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="InconsistentAsyncClockTickSize">The function-call block ''{0}'' is triggered by asynchronous S-functions specifying conflicting clock tick size: ''{1}'' specifies {2}, while ''{3}'' specifies {4}.</entry>
    <entry key="InconsistentAsyncClockTickDType">The function-call block ''{0}'' is triggered by asynchronous S-functions specifying conflicting clock tick data type: ''{1}'' specifies {2}, while ''{3}'' specifies {4}.</entry>
    <entry key="AsyncCustomCannotCombineWithOtherAsyc">The function-call block ''{0}'' is triggered by asynchronous S-functions specifying conflicting SS_OPTION: either ''{1}'' or ''{2}'' specifies SS_OPTION_ASYNCHRONOUS_CUSTOM while the other specifies SS_OPTION_ASYNCHRONOUS or SS_OPTION_ASYNCHRONOUS_INTERRUPT.}</entry>
    <entry key="InputPortSampleTimeMismatch">Sample time mismatch. Sample time ({0}) of signal driving input port {1,number,integer} of ''{2}'' differs from the required sample time ({3}) at this input port.</entry>
    <entry key="InvAsynSFuncLocation">All destinations of Asynchronous S-function ''{0}'' must be in the root system (i.e., destinations cannot be contained in conditionally executed subsystems).</entry>
    <entry key="InvAsyncInterruptSFcnLoc">S-function ''{0}'' and its function-call destination block must be in the root system or atomic subsystems because it has indicated that it is executing the destination function-call block asynchronously via a hardware interrupt.</entry>
     <entry key="InvAsyncRateTransIn">Because the block ''{0}'' is asynchronously executed, the source at input port {1,number,integer} must be a rate transition that inherits sample time at output port, or driven by a root input port that inherits sample time, or an asynchronous function call subsystem. Try inserting a rate transition block or make setting changes in the configuration parameters. If the block is driven by a function-call root Inport block, any root port that drives this block can't branch to drive other blocks. Consider splitting the branched root input port block into two to drive each of destination blocks separately. </entry>
    <entry key="InvalidAsyncTimeSourceCaller">The function-call block ''{0}'' is triggered by the asynchronous S-function ''{1}'', which specifies that it obtains its time from its caller.  However, any asynchronous S-function triggering a function-call block that has multiple triggers may not specify that it obtains its time from its caller.</entry>
    <entry key="InvBlkInPeriodicFCSS">''{0}'' has an invalid sample time. Only constant (inf), inherited (-1), or periodic ({1}) sample times are allowed in the periodic function-call block ''{2}''.</entry>
    <entry key="InvBlkInPeriodicAtomic">''{0}'' has an invalid sample time of {1}. Periodic atomic subsystem ''{2}'' may contain only blocks that have constant (inf), inherited (-1), or periodic ({3}) sample times. To resolve this issue, try to change the sample time with one of the following: \n \t - Configuring the block ''{4}'' to inherit the sample time  \n \t - Configuring the subsystem ''{5}''  to inherit the sample time. \nIf you cannot change the block sample time, remove the problem block from the subsystem. </entry>
    <entry key="InvAsyncRateTransOut">Because the block ''{0}'' is asynchronously executed, destination at output port {1,number,integer} must be a rate transition, or root output port that inherits sample time, or an asynchronous function-call subsystem.</entry>
	<entry key="InvAsyncRateTransOutHiddenToWksSigLog">Because the block ''{0}'' is asynchronously executed, signal cannot be logged at the destination of output port {1,number,integer}. To resolve this issue, either disable signal logging, insert a Rate Transition block and log the output of that block, or specify a sample time in 'Signal Properties' dialog.</entry>
	<entry key="InvAsyncRateTransOutHiddenToWksOutLog">Because the block ''{0}'' is asynchronously executed, output cannot be logged at the destination of output port {1,number,integer} in Dataset format. To resolve this issue, either insert a Rate Transition block before the root output port, or change Format configuration parameter to Array, Structure, or Structure with time.</entry>
    <entry key="InvAsyncRateTransBlkConn">Invalid connection for asynchronous rate transition ''{0}''. It should only be used when the source or destination is an asynchronously executed function-call block. In addition a direct connection between the asynchronous rate transition and the function-call block must exist (i.e., the signal connecting them cannot be observed).</entry>
    <entry key="InvTs">Sample time {0} of ''{1}'' is invalid.</entry>

    <entry key="InvPeriodOffsetPairFromSFcn">Sample time [{0} {1}] specified in
    the S-Function block ''{2}'' is invalid. Sample time must be a real double
    scalar (period) or a real double vector of length 2 (period, offset); where
    period, offset must be finite and non-negative and offset must be less than
    period.</entry>

    <entry key="InvTsInCaseSS">Sample time {0} of ''{1}'' does not match the sample time {2} of the SwitchCase block ''{3}'' controlling its execution.</entry>
    <entry key="InvTsInIfActionSS">Sample time {0} of ''{1}'' does not match the sample time {2} of the If block ''{3}'' controlling its execution.</entry>
    <entry key="InvTsParamSettingWithCause">In ''{0}'', the parameter ''{1}'' is not a valid sample time due to the cause attached.</entry>
    <entry key="InvTsDataStore">In ''{0}'', the parameter ''{1}'' is not a valid sample time because the data store ''{2}'' cannot be found.</entry>
    <entry key="InvTsParamSetting_Constant">In ''{0}'', the parameter ''{1}'' must be real and finite. Constant (inf) sample time is not allowed.</entry>
    <entry key="InvTsParamSetting_First_Element">In ''{0}'', the first element of the parameter ''{1}'' is {2}; this value is not permitted.</entry>
    <entry key="InvTsParamSetting_No_Continuous">The block ''{0}'' does not permit continuous sample time (0 or [0,0]) for the parameter ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="InvTsParamSetting_No_ZOHContinuous">The block ''{0}'' does not permit fixed-in-minor-step sample time ([0,1]) for the parameter ''{1}''.</entry>

    <entry key="InvTsParamSetting_Vector">
      In ''{0}'', the parameter ''{1}'' must be a real double scalar (period) or
      a real double vector of length 2 (period, offset); where period, offset
      must be finite and non-negative and offset must be less than period.
    </entry>

    <entry key="InvHybridIfactionSS">The block ''{0}'' is not allowed in an action subsystem because it has more than one sample time.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidInputPortTsInTrigSS">The S-function ''{0}'' has improperly set the sample time of input port {1,number,integer} when placed in the {2} subsystem ''{3}''</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidOutputPortTsInTrigSS">The S-function ''{0}'' has improperly set the sample time of output port {1,number,integer} when placed in the {2} subsystem ''{3}''</entry>
    <entry key="InvMRateBlkInPeriodicFCSS">''{0}'' has multiple sample times. Only constant (inf), inherited (-1), or periodic ({1}) sample times are allowed in the periodic function-call block ''{2}''.</entry>
    <entry key="InvMRateBlkInPeriodicAtomic">''{0}'' has multiple sample times. Only constant (inf), inherited (-1), or periodic ({1}) sample times are allowed in the periodic atomic subsystem ''{2}''.</entry>
    <entry key="InvMRateBlkInTrigSubsys">''{0}'' has multiple sample times. Only constant (inf) or inherited (-1) sample times are allowed in {1} subsystem ''{2}''.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidNegativeTsPeriod">The period ({0}) and offset ({1}) specified are not a valid sample time specification. The period may not be negative unless it is INHERITED_SAMPLE_TIME (-1).</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidNegativeTsPeriodAllowVariableTs">The period ({0}) and offset ({1}) specified are not a valid sample time specification. The period may not be negative unless it is either INHERITED_SAMPLE_TIME (-1) or VARIABLE_SAMPLE_TIME (-2).</entry>
    <entry key="InvBlkInAsyncFCSS">''{0}'' has an invalid sample time. Only constant (inf) or inherited (-1) sample times are allowed in the asynchronous subsystem ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="InvBlkInTrigSubsys2">''{0}'' has a discrete sample time because its trigger port block ''{1}'' sets its "Sample time type" to be "periodic". However, only constant (inf) or inherited (-1) sample times are allowed in {2} subsystem ''{3}''.  Set the "Sample time type" of that trigger port block to "triggered".</entry>
    <entry key="InvBlkInTrigSubsys">''{0}'' has sample time {1}. Only constant (inf) or inherited (-1) sample times are allowed in {2} subsystem ''{3}''.</entry>
    <entry key="InvSigLogTSInTrigSubsys">Cannot honor data logging Sample time ''{0}'' specified in 'Signal Properties'' dialog of output signals of block ''{1}''. Only constant (inf) or inherited (-1) sample times are allowed in {2} subsystem ''{3}''.</entry>
    <entry key="InvBlkInTrigModel">''{0}'' has sample time {1}. Only constant (inf) or inherited (-1) sample times are allowed in {2} model ''{3}''.</entry>
    <entry key="InvPortBasedModelBlkInTrigSubsys">The Model block ''{0}'' referencing model ''{1}'' has been improperly placed in the {2} subsystem ''{3}''. The model being referenced must inherit a sample time. Set the ''Periodic sample time constraint'' parameter to ''Ensure sample time independent'' on the Solver page of the Configuration Parameters for the model ''{4}'' and update the diagram to see why it does not inherit a sample time.</entry>
    <entry key="InvCallerTsForPeriodicFCSS">The caller ''{0}'' of function-call subsystem ''{1}'' has a sample time of {2} that does not match the periodic sample time {3} of the function-call subsystem.</entry>
    <entry key="InvConstCompTs">''{0}'' has an invalid constant (inf) sample time. Discrete states, continuous states, and tunable parameters are not allowed with constant sample times.</entry>

    <entry key="InvSFcnCallInitiatorTs">Invalid configuration at input port ''{0,number,integer}'' of  S-function block ''{1}''.  The block specifies the sample time {2} which is different than the sample time of its function call initiator ''{3}''</entry>
    <entry key="InvConstOffset">The period ({0}) and offset ({1}) specified are not a valid sample time specification. When the period is CONSTANT_SAMPLE_TIME (inf), the offset must be 0.</entry>
    <entry key="InvContOffset">The period ({0}) and offset ({1}) specified are not a valid sample time specification. When the period is CONTINUOUS_SAMPLE_TIME (0), the offset must be CONTINUOUS_SAMPLE_TIME (0) or  FIXED_IN_MINOR_STEP_OFFSET (1).</entry>
    <entry key="InvDiscOffsetTooBig">The period ({0}) and offset ({1}) specified are not a valid sample time specification. The offset must be less than the period.</entry>
    <entry key="InvNegOffset">The period ({0}) and offset ({1}) specified are not a valid sample time specification. The offset may not be negative.</entry>
    <entry key="InvNumTsForAsyncBlock">Invalid number of sample times registered by asynchronous ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="InvOffsetWithInheritedTs">The period ({0}) and offset ({1}) specified are not a valid sample time specification. When the period is INHERITED_SAMPLE_TIME (-1), the offset must be 0.</entry>
    <entry key="InvPortBasedSFcnBlkInTrigSubsys">''{0}'' has port-based sample times and has been improperly placed in the {1} subsystem ''{2}''. Port based sample time S-Functions may only be used in {3} subsystems if they specify the option SS_OPTION_ALLOW_PORT_SAMPLE_TIME_IN_TRIGSS.</entry>
    <entry key="InvPortBasedBlkInTrigSubsys">''{0}'' has been placed in the {1} subsystem ''{2}'' but does not support this configuration. Move the block out of the {3} subsystem.</entry>
    <entry key="InvInputPortTsInPeriodicFCSS">Port-based sample time block ''{0}'' has a sample time, {1}, on input port {2,number,integer} that does not align with the periodic sample time of function-call block ''{3}''. Only constant (inf), inherited (-1), or periodic ({4}) sample times are allowed in the block.</entry>
    <entry key="InvInputPortTsInPeriodicAtomic">Port-based sample time block ''{0}'' has a sample time, {1}, on input port {2,number,integer} that does not align with the periodic sample time of the atomic subsystem ''{3}''. Only constant (inf), inherited (-1), or periodic ({4}) sample times are allowed in the subsystem.</entry>
    <entry key="InvVarTsOffset">The period ({0}) and offset ({1}) specified are not a valid sample time specification. When the period is VARIABLE_SAMPLE_TIME (-2), the offset must be 0.</entry>
    <entry key="InvOutputPortTsInPeriodicFCSS">Port-based sample time block ''{0}'' has a sample time, {1}, on output port {2,number,integer} that does not align with the periodic sample time of function-call block ''{3}''. Only constant (inf), inherited (-1), or periodic ({4}) sample times are allowed in the block.</entry>
    <entry key="InvOutputPortTsInPeriodicAtomic">Port-based sample time block ''{0}'' has a sample time, {1}, on output port {2,number,integer} that does not align with the periodic sample time of the atomic subsystem ''{3}''. Only constant (inf), inherited (-1), or periodic ({4}) sample times are allowed in the subsystem.</entry>
    <entry key="MultiTaskDSM">The blocks ''{0}'' and ''{1}'' are accessing the Data Store Memory block ''{2}''.  
    The two blocks execute in different tasks, which can lead to a lack of data integrity 
    in a multi-tasking, real-time environment.  Consider adjusting the sample times of the 
    blocks that access that data store. Alternatively, set the ''Configuration 
    Parameters > Diagnostics > Data Validity > Multitask data store'' parameter to ''none'' if the data store 
    is accessed with an atomic operation, or if the tasks involved cannot preempt each other in the target system.</entry>

    <entry key="MultiTaskDSMSingleBlock">The block ''{0}'' is accessing the Data Store Memory block ''{1}'' and executes in multiple tasks. This can lead to a lack of data integrity in a multi-tasking, real-time environment. Set the ''Configuration Parameters > Diagnostics > Data Validity > Multitask data store'' parameter to ''none'' if the data store is accessed with an atomic operation, or if the tasks involved cannot preempt each other in the target system.</entry>

    <entry key="MultiTsGlobalDSM">In model ''{0}'', blocks ''{1}'' and ''{2}'' are accessing a global data 
    store defined by the global Simulink.Signal object ''{3}''.  The two blocks execute in different tasks,
    which can lead to a lack of data integrity in a multi-tasking, real-time environment.  Consider 
    adjusting the sample times of the blocks that 
    access that data store. Alternatively, set the ''Configuration Parameters > Diagnostics > 
    Data Validity > Multitask data store'' parameter to ''none'' if the data store is accessed with an 
    atomic operation, or if the tasks involved cannot preempt each other in the target system.</entry>

    <entry key="MultiTsGlobalDSMSingleBlock">In model ''{0}'', the Model block ''{1}'' directly or indirectly 
    references a model containing blocks that are configured to execute in multiple tasks, and that are 
    accessing a global data store defined by the global Simulink.Signal object 
    ''{2}''.  This can lead to a lack of data integrity in a multi-tasking, real-time environment.  Consider 
    adjusting the sample times of the blocks that access that data store. 
    Alternatively, set the ''Configuration Parameters > Diagnostics > Data Validity > Multitask data store'' 
    parameter to ''none'' if the data store is accessed with an atomic operation, or if the tasks involved 
    cannot preempt each other in the target system.</entry>
    <entry key="MustUseVariableStepSolver">Fixed-step solver ''{0}'' cannot be used for hybrid block diagram ''{1}'' because it contains S-functions with variable sample times.</entry>
    <entry key="MT_DSMMsgMustBeErrorForConcurrentTasks">Since 'Concurrent tasks' mode is selected, you must set the diagnostic option 'Multitask data store' on the 'Data validity' pane to 'error'</entry>
    <entry key="MT_CondExeSysMustBeErrorForConcurrentTasks">Since 'Concurrent tasking' mode is selected, you must set the diagnostic option 'Multitask conditionally executed subsystem' on the 'Sample time' pane to 'error'</entry>
    <entry key="MT_RateTransMustBeErrorForConcurrentTasks">Since 'Concurrent tasking' mode is selected, you must set the diagnostic option 'Multitask rate transition' on the 'Sample time' pane to 'error'</entry>
    <entry key="MultirateSfcnWritesToGlobalDSM">The S-Function block ''{0}'' has multiple rates, yet accesses the global data store ''{1}''; S-Functions accessing global data stores must be single rate.</entry>
    <entry key="MultiTrigWithoutPriority">The function-call block ''{0}'' has multiple asynchronous triggers that do not specify priority.  Data integrity will not be maintained if these triggers can preempt one another.</entry>
    <entry key="MuxedSyncAndAsyncTriggers">''{0}'' may not be used to combine an asynchronous function call with data or a synchronous function call.</entry>
    <entry key="NeedRewireOrManuallyInsertRateTransBlkInput">Simulink detected an unspecified rate transition at input port {0,number,integer} of block ''{1}''. However, Simulink cannot automatically insert a Rate Transition block because one of the following scenarios exists: \n - Fixing the unspecified rate transition requires rewiring of the blocks;\n - Simulink cannot choose an insertion location for the Rate Transition block because multiple possibilities exist; \n - The unspecified rate transition requires the insertion of a Rate Transition block on a virtual bus signal. \n - The input signal of this block is being logged. \n - Either the source or destination is a state port. \n Rewire the block diagram or manually insert a Rate Transition block to resolve the unspecified rate transition.</entry>
    <entry key="NeedRewireOrManuallyInsertRateTransBlkOutput">Simulink detected an unspecified rate transition at output port {0,number,integer} of block ''{1}''. However, Simulink cannot automatically insert a Rate Transition block because one of the following scenarios exists: \n - Fixing the unspecified rate transition requires rewiring of the blocks;\n - Simulink cannot choose an insertion location for the Rate Transition block because multiple possibilities exist; \n - The unspecified rate transition requires the insertion of a Rate Transition block on a virtual bus signal. \n - The output signal of this block is being logged. \n - Either the source or destination is a state port. \n Rewire the block diagram or manually insert a Rate Transition block to resolve the unspecified rate transition.</entry>
    <entry key="NeedRewireOrManuallyInsertRateTransBlkEnablePort">Simulink detected an unspecified rate transition at enable port block ''{0}''. However, Simulink cannot automatically insert a Rate Transition block because one of the following scenarios exists: \n - Fixing the unspecified rate transition requires rewiring of the blocks;\n - Simulink cannot choose an insertion location for the Rate Transition block because multiple possibilities exist; \n - The unspecified rate transition requires the insertion of a Rate Transition block on a virtual bus signal. \n - The output signal of this block is being logged. \n - Either the source or destination is a state port. \n Rewire the block diagram or manually insert a Rate Transition block to resolve the unspecified rate transition.</entry>
    <entry key="NoTsInhDueToPreSetBlkTs">This model will not inherit a sample time because a sample time was explicitly set in block ''{0}''.\n \n If this model does not need to inherit a sample time, change the "Periodic sample time constraint" to something other than "Ensure sample time independent" on the Solver tab of the Configuration Parameters dialog.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidExportPerodicConnection">Invalid connection starts with S-function ''{0}'', which is making a function call on output port element {1,number,integer}. A function call generator must drive a function call port of a subsystem or a Model block. </entry>
    <entry key="NoTsBlockReduced">Since block ''{0}'' has been removed from the compiled version of the model, Simulink cannot access its sample time information. To obtain the sample time information for this block, turn off BlockReduction on the "All Parameters" tab of the Configuration Parameters dialog box.</entry>
    <entry key="NoMoreSampleTimeColors">The model has {0,number,integer} discrete rates, which is greater than the {1,number,integer} discrete sample time colors available.  The {2,number,integer}th and slower rates have been marked using the orange sample time color.</entry>
    <entry key="NoMultiTasking">Model ''{0}'' does not contain multiple sample times. You must specify solver mode as Auto or SingleTasking.</entry>
    <entry key="NoMultiTaskingTid01eq">Model ''{0}'' does not contain multiple sample times. This model contains a continuous and a discrete sample time which are the same rate. You must specify solver mode as Auto or SingleTasking.</entry>
    <entry key="NoRateCheckForMultiRateSFcn">Unable to check for valid rate transitions in S-function {0} of ''{1}'' since it has multiple block based sample times and no port sample times. You should update your S-function to specify port sample times.</entry>
    <entry key="NotCombinableAsyncPeriodicTsAtBlk">A port of ''{0}'' is being invoked with asynchronous rate and periodic rate. Asynchronous rate can not be combined with other type of sample times. </entry>
    <entry key="NotCombinableSignalAndMessagesRelatedTsAtBlk">''{0}'' block accepts one or more inputs of type Simulink Messages payload and periodic rate signals. This block can accept only either of them. </entry>
    <entry key="NotCombinableForAsyncSfcnNotSpecifyPrioirty">The asynchronous function-call signal initiated by S-Function ''{0}'' cannot be combined with other asynchronous rates because the S-function has not set a priority for the asynchronous rate.</entry>
    <entry key="NotCombinableForAsyncSfcnNotUsingBaseRateTimer">The asynchronous function-call signal initiated by S-Function ''{0}'' cannot be combined with other asynchronous rates because the S-function does not set the asynchronous rate to use the base rate timer.</entry>
    <entry key="NoTsInhDueToAbsTimeUnknownSource">This model will not inherit a sample time because either at least one block requires absolute time or at least one signal in the model uses signal logging. \n \n If this model does not need to inherit a sample time, change the Configuration Parameters > Solver > Periodic sample time constraint parameter to an option other than "Ensure sample time independent".</entry>
    <entry key="NoTsInhDueToBlock">This model will not inherit a sample time because the block ''{0}'' disallows it from doing so. \n \n If this model does not need to inherit a sample time, change the "Periodic sample time constraint" to something other than "Ensure sample time independent" on the Solver tab of the Configuration Parameters dialog.</entry>
    <entry key="NoTsInhDueToBlkNeedsAbsTime">This model will not inherit a sample time because ''{0}'' uses absolute time. \n \n If this model does not need to inherit a sample time, change the "Periodic sample time constraint" to something other than "Ensure sample time independent" on the Solver tab of the Configuration Parameters dialog.</entry>
    <entry key="NoTsInhDueToSpecifiedFixedStepSize">This model will not inherit a sample time because the fixed step size was explicitly set for the model.\n \n If this model does not need to inherit a sample time, change the "Periodic sample time constraint" to something other than "Ensure sample time independent" on the Solver tab of the Configuration Parameters dialog.</entry>
    <entry key="NoTsInhDueToNoInsAndOnlyConstOuts">This model will not inherit a sample time because there are no input ports and all of the output ports have a constant (inf) sample time. \n \n If this model does not need to inherit a sample time, change the "Periodic sample time constraint" to something other than "Ensure sample time independent" on the Solver tab of the Configuration Parameters dialog.</entry>
    <entry key="NoTsInhDueToMultiTs">This model will not inherit a sample time because there are multiple sample times in the model.  \n \n If this model does not need to inherit a sample time, change the "Periodic sample time constraint" to something other than "Ensure sample time independent" on the Solver tab of the Configuration Parameters dialog.</entry>
    <entry key="NoTsInhDueToContinuousTs">This model will not inherit a sample time because there is a continuous sample time in the model.  \n \n If this model does not need to inherit a sample time, change the "Periodic sample time constraint" to something other than "Ensure sample time independent" on the Solver tab of the Configuration Parameters dialog.</entry>
    <entry key="NoVariablePortBasedTs">Variable sample times cannot be assigned to ports in ''{0}''.</entry>  
    <entry key="NvBusBlkInputSampleTimeMismatch">Sample time mismatch.  When a Bus Creator or Bus Assignment block outputs a nonvirtual bus, all of the signals driving its input ports must have the same sample time.  This restriction applies even if the elements of the object defining the bus specify an inherited (-1) sample time. The sample time ({0}) of the signal driving input port {1,number,integer} of ''{2}'' does not match the sample time ({3}) of the block.</entry>
    <entry key="SfcnTimerOverFlow"><![CDATA[Asynchronous timer defined in S-function ''{0}'' will overflow in {1} days. Considering choosing larger timer data type size or larger timer clocktick stepsize in the S-function or choosing a smaller value for the ''Application lifespan (days)'' option in the Optimization page of the Configuration Parameters Dialog. You can also consider disabling the message by choosing ''None'' for the (''Diagnostics'' > ''Data Validity'' > ''Signals'' >) ''Detect overflow'' option in the Configuration Parameters dialog]]></entry>
    <entry key="SfcnSpecifyTooLongTimerForIntegerOnlyCode">Asynchronous S-function block ''{0}'' specifies 64-bit timer. Generate code must support floating-point numbers to hold value of a 64-bit timer. Consider specifying smaller timer in Asynchronous S-function or checking Support ''Floating-point numbers'' option on Code Generation -> Interface pane</entry>
    <entry key="SharedAsyncPriority">The function-call block ''{0}'' has multiple asynchronous triggers specifying equal priorities. Set the Tasks with equal priority option in the Diagnostics page of the Configuration Parameters Dialog to "none" if tasks of equal priority can not preempt each other in the target system.</entry>
    <entry key="SigspecInputSampleTimeMismatch">Sample time mismatch. Sample time ({0}) of signal at output port {1,number,integer} of ''{2}'' does not match the sample time ({3}) specified for this signal by ''{4}''.  Consider using a Rate Transition block to resolve the mismatch.  To turn off reporting of this condition, change the value of the ''Enforce sample times specified by Signal Specification blocks'' parameter in the Sample Time group of the Diagnostics pane of the Configuration Parameters dialog box to ''none''.</entry>
    <entry key="SigspecOutputSampleTimeMismatch">Sample time mismatch. Sample time ({0}) of signal at input port {1,number,integer} of ''{2}'' does not match the sample time ({3}) specified for this signal by ''{4}''.  Consider using a Rate Transition block to resolve the mismatch.  To turn off reporting of this condition, change the value of the ''Enforce sample times specified by Signal Specification blocks'' parameter in the Sample Time group of the Diagnostics pane of the Configuration Parameters dialog box to ''none''.</entry>
    <entry key="SlowEnableToFastSubsys">Sample time of enable signal feeding subsystem ''{0}'' is slower than sample times within the enabled subsystem. This can result in nondeterministic behavior in a multitasking real-time system. Consider adding a Rate Transition followed by a Signal Specification with a sample time equal to the enable signal rate.</entry>
    <entry key="SourceInheritedTS">Source ''{0}'' specifies that its sample time (-1) is back-inherited. You should explicitly specify the sample time of sources. You can disable this diagnostic by setting the ''Source block specifies -1 sample time'' diagnostic to ''none'' in the Sample Time group on the Diagnostics pane of the Configuration Parameters dialog box.</entry>
    <entry key="InheritedIndexedRateAfterProp">Block ''{0}'' should not have any inherited indexed sample times after sample time propagation.</entry>
    <entry key="SpecifyTsPriorityForModelRef">Simulink does not allow explicit specification of sample time priority for a model reference target. Consider changing the Solver parameter ''Periodic sample time constraint'' to ''Unconstrained''.</entry>
    <entry key="TmpModelDisallowTsInheritInRightClickBuild">Since the right click build subsystem is in a triggered or function call subsystem in original model, generated S-function block must inherit sample time to match its behavior. However, the subsystem disallows inherited sample time because of reasons reported in following error messages. Consider: \n - Removing blocks that disallow sample time inheritance; \n - Moving the subsystem out of the triggered subsystem in original model.</entry>
    <entry key="OutputPortMixedSampleTime">The output port {0,number,integer} of the subsystem ''{1}'' is connected to a signal with mixed sample times and therefore not supported for subsystem based code generation.</entry>
    <entry key="RTBUnitDelayAtRightClickBuildBoundary">Since the block ''{0}'' is inside a right click build subsystem ''{1}'' and all its destination blocks are outside of the subsystem. Generated code from right click build will behave differently than original subsystem. Consider moving the block outside of the right click build system, or moving at least one destination block in the subsystem.</entry>
    <entry key="TooLargeRatioBaseRateSubRate">The periodic sample time {0} is not allowed because the ratio of this sample time over base rate ({1}) is greater than the maximum value of uint32.</entry>
    <entry key="TooLongTimerForIntegerOnlyCode">Generated code doesn''t support floating-point numbers. Integer timer of TID {0,number,integer} will overflow during model ''Application life span (days)''. Consider choosing smaller value for ''Application life span(days)'' parameter specified in the Optimization page of the Configuration Parameters dialog, or checking support ''Floating-point numbers'' option on Code Generation > Interface pane</entry>
    <entry key="TsClashesErr_s">Two sample times in ''{0}'' are considered identical due to very small difference between them. This results in repeated (duplicate) sample times which is not allowed.</entry>
    <entry key="TsMismatchForTsDepModelBlk">The Model Reference block ''{0}'' is triggered using a sample time {1}. This value is inconsistent with the sample time {2} specified by the referenced model ''{3}'' on the Solver tab of the Configuration Parameters dialog. These two sample times must be identical.</entry>
    <entry key="TsOffsetMustBeFinite">The period ({0}) and offset ({1}) specified are not a valid sample time specification. The offset must be finite.</entry>
    <entry key="TsPropEnabOutputsChangeNotAligned">Signal from outport ''{0}'', which is configured to reset when disabled, can change at times that do not align with the signal''s sample time due to the enable signal which is executing at a faster rate.</entry>
    <entry key="TsRepeatedErr">Repeated (duplicate) sample times were registered by ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="TooManyContTs">More than one continuous sample times specified for ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="TooManyVariableTs">''{0}'' can have only one variable sample time.</entry>
    <entry key="TsPeriodCannotBeNaN">The period ({0}) and offset ({1}) specified are not a valid sample time specification. The period cannot be NaN.</entry>
    <entry key="TsPropertiesIsEmpty">Solver page ''Sample time properties'' is empty or in invalid format. Fill this field or don''t choose ''Specify'' in ''Periodic sample time constraint''.</entry>
    <entry key="TsPropTsNotSet">Sample time for ''{0}'' output {1,number,integer} was not set.</entry>

    <entry key="TSSpecifiedMisMatchPropTS">
      At least one sample time in the model is not found in the sample time
      properties specified on the Solver page. The periodic sample time
      constraints specified are: {0}, where as the periodic sample times in the
      model are: {1}.
    </entry>

    <entry key="TSSpecifiesInWrongOrder">At least one sample time is specified in wrong order in the sample time properties on the Solver page. The periodic sample time {0} is slower than the sample time {1}. All sample times must be ordered from fast to slow.</entry>
    <entry key="TwoAsyncTIDsAssignedSamePriority">Asynchronous tasks associated with S-functions ''{0}'' and ''{1}'' are assigned the same priority: {2,number,integer}. Either modify these S-functions to specify differing priorities, or set the Tasks with equal priority option in the Diagnostics page of the Configuration Parameters Dialog to "none" if tasks of equal priority can not preempt each other in the target system.</entry>
    <entry key="TwoAsyncTaskSpecTIDsAssignedSamePriority">Asynchronous tasks associated with Asynchronous Task Specification blocks ''{0}'' and ''{1}'' are assigned the same priority: {2,number,integer}. Either modify these blocks to specify differing priorities, or set the Tasks with equal priority option in the Diagnostics page of the Configuration Parameters Dialog to "none" if tasks of equal priority can not preempt each other in the target system.</entry>
    <entry key="TwoSyncTIDsAssignedSamePriority">Two periodic tasks may not share the same priority. The tasks with sample time {0} and sample time {1} are assigned the same priority: {2,number,integer}.</entry>
    <entry key="UnsetPortTs">The sample time for output port {0,number,integer} of port-based ''{1}'' is unset. All the input port sample times have been set. Specify a sample time on a block driven by this output.</entry>
    <entry key="VarSTOutPortIsFrameBased">Output port {0,number,integer} of ''{1}'' is set to be frame-based even though this port has a variable sample time. Frame-based signals should have a discrete sample time.</entry>
    <entry key="VariableSTBlkHasFrames">One or more ports of block ''{0}'' are set to be frame-based even though this block has a variable sample time.  Frame-based signals should have a discrete sample time.</entry>
    <entry key="VariableTsWithSFunctionTarget">''{0}'' has a variable sample time. Variable sample times are not supported by the S-Function Target.</entry>
    <entry key="VariableStepTsNotAllowed">Cannot compile diagram ''{0}'' because it contains variable sample times or S-functions and is using a fixed-step solver.</entry>
    <entry key="BlkNotSupportConcurrentTasks"> The block ''{0}'' has multiple rates, hence the block may run on multiple concurrent tasks. However the block is not compliant with concurrent tasks mode. The block must be updated to support concurrent execution. Alternatively, consider configuring the model in single tasking or multitasking (nonconcurrent) mode. </entry>
    <entry key="VariableSampleTimeDescription">Variable {0,number,integer}</entry>
    <entry key="TriggeredSampleTimeDescription">Triggered</entry>
    <entry key="HybridSampleTimeDescription">Hybrid</entry>
    <entry key="UnionSampleTimeDescription">Union {0,number,integer}</entry>
    <entry key="AsyncSampleTimeDescription">Asynchronous {0,number,integer}</entry>
    <entry key="EventSampleTimeDescription">Event</entry>
    <entry key="PowerUpSampleTimeDescription">Initialize</entry>
    <entry key="RunTimeSampleTimeDescription">RunTime</entry>
    <entry key="ResetSampleTimeDescription">Reset</entry>
    <entry key="ResetWithInitSampleTimeDescription">Reset With Initialize</entry>
    <entry key="PowerDownSampleTimeDescription">Terminate</entry>
    <entry key="GenericAsyncSampleTimeDescription">Asynchronous Hybrid</entry>
    <entry key="PeriodicSampleTimeDescription">Discrete {0,number,integer}</entry>
    <entry key="ContinuousDescription">Continuous</entry>
    <entry key="ExportInheritSampleTimeDescription"> Exported Inherit </entry>
    <entry key="ExportPeriodicSampleTimeDescription"> Exported Discrete </entry>
    <entry key="InternalInheritError">An internal error occurred calculating the sample time inheritance rule for this model. Please report this bug to MathWorks Technical Support.</entry>
    <entry key="SameVarTsUIDInBlk"> Block ''{0}'' cannot have two variable sample times with the same unique ID. Each variable sample time in one block must have its own unique ID.</entry>
    <entry key="ReCompileSFcn"> To use block ''{0}'' in referenced models, recompile the S-function with the current version of Simulink.</entry>
    <entry key="ModelWideEventWithUpdateFcn"> The block ''{0}'' has an Update Function and has been assigned the same time {1}. These settings are not compatible. The update function will not be called.</entry>
    <entry key="SampleTimeTypeSpecificationMismatchPeriodicWasInherited"> In ''{0}'', the parameter ''{1}'' specified a sample time type of ''Periodic'', but the evaluated sample time type was ''Inherited''. Update the sample time type or the sample time value to ensure consistency.</entry>
    <entry key="SampleTimeTypeSpecificationMismatchPeriodicWasConstant"> In ''{0}'', the parameter ''{1}'' specified a sample time type of ''Periodic'', but the evaluated sample time type was ''Constant''. Update the sample time type or the sample time value to ensure consistency.</entry>
    <entry key="SampleTimeTypeSpecificationMismatchPeriodicWasParameter"> In ''{0}'', the parameter ''{1}'' specified a sample time type of ''Periodic'', but the evaluated sample time type was ''Parameter''. Update the sample time type or the sample time value to ensure consistency.</entry>
    <entry key="SampleTimeTypeSpecificationMismatchPeriodicWasContinuous"> In ''{0}'', the parameter ''{1}'' specified a sample time type of ''Periodic'', but the evaluated sample time type was ''Continuous''. Update the sample time type or the sample time value to ensure consistency.</entry>
    <entry key="SampleTimeTypePeriodicWithoutValidSampleTime"> In ''{0}'', ''{1}'' should be a positive finite number, but ''{2}'' was specified. Either specify a valid number, or change ''{3}'' to ''{4}''.</entry>
    <entry key="SampleTimeTypeDisallowed"> In ''{0}'', the parameter ''{1}'' does not allow a sample time type of {2}.</entry>
    <entry key="InvTsParamSetting_ExplicitSubsystemTaskingNonPeriodic"> <![CDATA[Block ''{0}'' specifies an explicit <sldiag objui="blockdlg" objparam="SystemEntryPoint">entry point</sldiag>, but has a non periodic <sldiag objui="blockdlg" objparam="SystemSampleTime">sample time</sldiag>. Specified sample times must be periodic when using explicit entry points.]]></entry>
    <entry key="SampleTimeWidgetTypeParameter">Parameter</entry>
    <entry key="SampleTimeWidgetTypeConstant">Constant</entry>
    <entry key="SampleTimeWidgetTypeUnresolved"><![CDATA[<From Value>]]></entry>
    <entry key="SampleTimeWidgetTypeInherited">Inherited</entry>
    <entry key="SampleTimeWidgetTypeContinuous">Continuous</entry>
    <entry key="SampleTimeWidgetTypePeriodic">Periodic</entry>
    <entry key="SampleTimeWidgetTooltipCombobox">Select the sample time type. To specify an unknown sample time from a variable, select ''{0}''.</entry>
    <entry key="SampleTimeWidgetTooltipPeriodic">Enter a periodic sample time. Values can be either a period expressed as a positive finite double, or a two element vector containing a period and an offset.</entry>
    <entry key="SampleTimeWidgetTooltipUnresolved">Enter a sample time. Values can be either a double, or a two element vector of doubles.</entry>
    <entry key="SampleTimeWidgetTooltipOther">The current integer value of the sample time.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidTaskDependencyRTB">A task dependency is not permitted between ''{0}'' and ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="GenericError">Generic error {0}. Please report this as a bug.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidBlockConnectToIRTInport">Block ''{0}'' output port {1,number,integer} is connected to an Initialize, Reset, or Terminate Function block ''{2}'' input port {3,number,integer}. Only Inport blocks are allowed to connect to the input ports of an Initialize, Reset, or Terminate Function block.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidBlockConnectToIRTInportMdlRef">Block ''{0}'' output port {1,number,integer} is connected to an Initialize, Reset, or Terminate Function block inside Model block ''{2}'' via input port {3,number,integer}. Only Inport blocks are allowed to connect to the input ports of an Initialize, Reset, and Terminate Function block. If the Model block resides in the topmost model hierarchy and is referencing an export function model saved in R2016b or later, you can select the option ''{4}'', ''{5}'', or ''{6}'' for the Model block that corresponds to the function type to remove this restriction.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidBlockConnectToIRTOutport">Block ''{0}'' input port {1,number,integer} is connected to an Initialize, Reset, or Terminate Function block ''{2}'' output port {3,number,integer}. Only Outport blocks are allowed to connect to the output ports of an Initialize, Reset, or Terminate Function block; Connections to Merge blocks are allowed within export function models.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidBlockConnectToIRTOutportMdlRef">Block ''{0}'' input port {1,number,integer} is connected to Initialize, Reset, or Terminate Function block inside Model block ''{2}'' via output port {3,number,integer}. Only Outport blocks are allowed to connect to the output ports of an Initialize, Reset, or Terminate Function block; Connections to Merge blocks are allowed within export function models. If the Model block resides in the topmost model hierarchy and is referencing an export function model saved in R2016b or later, you can select the option ''{4}'', ''{5}'', or ''{6}'' for the Model block that corresponds to the function type to remove this restriction.</entry>
    <entry key="InitResetTermEventMustMergeWithOtherRate">A port of ''{0}'' is being invoked with only Initialize, Reset, or Terminate Functions. This is not allowed.</entry>    
    <entry key="InitTermFunctionOnlySupportsNormalAndRTWCodeGen">Currently, only normal simulation and code generation are supported for a model containing Initialize, Terminate or Reset Function blocks.</entry>
    <entry key="InitTermFunctionDoesNotSupportModelRefAccelMode">Only normal mode simulation is supported for a model block that references a model containing Initialize, Terminate or Reset Function blocks.</entry>
    <entry key="InitTermFunctionDoesNotSupportCPPCodeGen">Code Generation using the C++ interface is not supported in models containing the Initialize, Reset or Terminate Function blocks.</entry>
    <entry key="InitTermFunctionDoesNotSupportCustomCode">Addition of custom initialization and custom termination code using the 'Configuration Parameters > Code Generation > Custom Code' dialog is not supported in models containing the Initialize, Reset or Terminate Function blocks.</entry>
    <entry key="ModelBlockNoTerminatePortForTermInput">The option ''{0}'' must be selected in addition to the option ''{1}'' for Model block ''{2}'' because its input port {3,number,integer} is connected to a Terminate Function block inside the referenced model.</entry>
    <entry key="ModelBlockNoTerminatePortForTermOutput">The option ''{0}'' must be selected in addition to the option ''{1}'' for Model block ''{2}'' because its output port {3,number,integer} is connected to a Terminate Function block inside the referenced model.</entry>
    <entry key="IRTInportBranching">Block ''{0}'' connecting to input ports of Initialize, Reset or Terminate Functions ''{1}'' must inherit sample time and can't branch.</entry>
    <entry key="InvRateBlkInIRTSubsys">Block ''{0}'' has a sample time which is not permitted in ''{1}''.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidBlockRateinIRTSubsys">The block ''{0}'' has a sample time of ''{1}''. Only constant (inf) or inherited (-1) sample times are allowed in Initialize, Reset or Terminate Functions.</entry>
   </message>
</rsccat>

<!-- LocalWords:  xml UTF CDATA sle Acc uncheck preactivation ashow DTYPE
     LocalWords:  DSTATES RWORK IWORK PWORK datatypes testpoint Jc nonvirtual
     LocalWords:  SIL Unbuffer PWork demultiplexed checksums Deriv etrace elist
     LocalWords:  sid atrace bafter mth bshow ebreak emode ishow strace
     LocalWords:  nanbreak rbreak slist blockmth stimes tbreak Tj Tz Hs Izc
     LocalWords:  undisp untrace winreuse xbreak zcbreak zclist CSTATE Zc Evnt
     LocalWords:  Sgnl UDI uploadable dworks extmode Intrf matfile Inp subsys
     LocalWords:  DF directfeed HMI slfeature suboption DSTATE TRIGSS unapplied
     LocalWords:  SCD scrollbar Ds linearizing Metadata grt uncompiled th
     LocalWords:  TIMESPAN DWork Dlg overwritable discontiguous PLC datatype
     LocalWords:  reusability bitfields UDD AUTOSAR Bitsets bitsets Prms
     LocalWords:  aliasedthrough tunabilities sfundemo superset WKS resave slvr
     LocalWords:  Zcs hmin Demuxes sfunction unselecting Nonreused nonreused
     LocalWords:  TFL UI pri modelname nondiscrete noncustom runnables
     LocalWords:  inheritability clocktick stepsize nonconcurrent
-->
