<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2009-2016 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="Simulink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../../matlab/resources/schema/msgcat.xsd">
  <message>
      
    <!-- From Workspace Errors -->
    <entry key="FromwksNoExtrapWithoutInterp">Invalid value specified for parameter ''{0}'' in ''{1}''.  Cannot extrapolate data after final data value unless the interpolate checkbox is turned on.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksUnsupportedDimensions">Invalid structure-format variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''.  The structure''s ''dimensions'' field must be a scalar or a vector with 2 elements. In addition, this field must be compatible with the dimensions of input signal stored in the ''values'' field.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksDifferentNumRows">Invalid structure-format variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. Time and data values must have the same number of rows</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksDifferentNumRows2">Invalid structure-format variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. Values in valueDimensions field and data values must have the same number of rows.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksDifferentNumTSteps">Invalid structure-format variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. The last dimension of each ''signals.values'' field must be the same as the number of rows in the ''time'' field.</entry>
    <entry key="BlockNotSupportedWithDictionary">This model cannot contain {0} block ''{1}'' because the model is linked to a data dictionary.  For a test harness model, configure it to use the base workspace instead of a data dictionary.  Otherwise, replace this block with a root Inport or other source block.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksDifferentNumTSteps2">Invalid structure-format variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. The last dimension of each ''signals.values'' field must be the same as the number of rows in the ''valueDimensions'' field.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksVarDimsNumDimsMismatch">Invalid structure-format variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. The number of columns of values in the ''valueDimensions'' field does not match the number of dimensions specified by signal data.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksInvTimeValues">Invalid workspace variable ''{0}'' specified as {1} input in ''{2}''. Time values must be a real vector.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksInvMatrixParam">Invalid variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. The variable is either a matrix or is a Simulink.SimulationData.Dataset object with an element containing matrix data. The matrix data must be a real, double, have two dimensions, and at least two columns. The first column must contain time values and the remaining columns the data values.  Matrix values cannot be Inf or NaN.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksNonMontonicTime_ss">Invalid workspace variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. Time values must be non-decreasing.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksCyclicOnlyWithNoTime">Cannot specify cyclic repetition in ''{0}'' when the time vector is explicitly specified for the data. The cyclic option is supported only when the data is in the form of a structure with an empty time vector.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksUnsupportedDataType">Invalid structure-format variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. Only numeric, logical and enumerated values are supported. Data must be finite (not Inf or NaN). </entry>
    <entry key="FromwksInfValueInParam">Invalid data values within variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. Data values must neither be Inf nor NaN. Also, the values should be specified using matrices that are neither empty nor sparse.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksDiscCannotInterp">Invalid setting for parameter ''{0}'' in ''{1}''. When time field is not specified in ''{2}'' parameter, interpolation has to be turned off and the extrapolation option cannot be chosen for forming the output after the final data value.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksVarDimsCannotInterpWithTime">Invalid setting for parameter ''{0}'' in ''{1}''. When the workspace contains a variable-size signal, deselect the "Interpolate data" checkbox and the parameter "Form output after final data value by" can only be set to "Hold final value".</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksVarDimsCannotInterpWithoutTime">Invalid setting for parameter ''{0}'' in ''{1}''. When the workspace contains a variable-size signal, deselect the "Interpolate data" checkbox and the parameter "Form output after final data value by" can only be set to "Hold final value" or "Cyclic repetition".</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksVarDimsCannotZeroCrossing">Invalid setting for parameter ''{0}'' in ''{1}''. When workspace contains a variable-size signal, deselect the "Enable zero-crossing detection" checkbox.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksVarDimsFinalValWithTime">Invalid setting for parameter ''{0}'' in ''{1}''. When the workspace contains a variable-size signal, the "Form output after final data value by" parameter can only be set to "Hold final value".</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksVarDimsFinalValWithoutTime">Invalid setting for parameter ''{0}'' in ''{1}''. When the workspace contains a variable-size signal, the "Form output after final data value by" parameter can only be set to "Hold final value" or "Cyclic repetition".</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksCannotInterpFiOrEnum">Invalid setting for parameter ''{0}'' in ''{1}''. The variable ''{2}'' cannot be interpolated.  When the ''{3}'' parameter refers to a workspace variable that contains fi or enumeration data, interpolation must be turned off and the extrapolation option cannot be chosen for forming the output after the final data value.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksUndefinedDataField">Invalid structure-format variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. If the input signal is a bus signal, the variable must be a structure of MATLAB timeseries objects. Otherwise, the variable must include ''time'' and ''signals'' field, and the ''signals'' field must be a structure with a ''values'' fields.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksMultipleSignals">Invalid structure-format variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. The ''signals'' structure has {2,number,integer} elements instead of {3,number,integer} elements.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksTsArrayNotSupported">Invalid TsArray object specified as input to ''{0}''. The From Workspace block does not support TsArray objects.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksTimeseriesStructNotSupported">Invalid structure specified as input to ''{0}''. The From Workspace block does not support structure of timeseries objects.</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksNotSupportedFormat">Unsupported input format for From Workspace block ''{0}''. Available formats are double non-complex matrix, a structure with or without time, or a structure with MATLAB timeseries as leaf nodes. All formats require the data to be finite (not Inf or NaN).</entry>
    <entry key="FromwksOnlyDiscSampleTime">Invalid continuous sample time specified for ''{0}''. Continuous sample time is not permitted when the input from workspace is a structure with no time data. To eliminate this error, select a discrete sample time or change the input data to include time data.</entry>

    <entry key="FromWksStrictBusMode">
        <![CDATA[The From Workspace block ''{0}'' is configured to load a bus signal. Bus signals may only be loaded if the strict bus modeling diagnostic is set to ''Error''. To load this bus signal, change Configuration Parameters -> Diagnostics -> Connectivity -> Mux blocks used to create bus signals to ''Error''.]]>
    </entry>
    <entry key="FromWksDataTypeMismatch">Inconsistent data type for From Workspace block ''{0}''.  The workspace variable has data type ''{1}''.  This data type does not agree with the data type, ''{2}'', that is being set for this block.  Change the data type of the input data to ''{3}'' or change the "Output data type" of this block to ''Inherit: auto''.</entry>
    <entry key="FromWksFastRestartDimensionsMismatch">The dimensions of data for block ''{0}'' specified for this Fast Restart run are different from the dimensions used in the previous Fast Restart run. To run in Fast Restart mode again, use data with dimensions that match those of the From Workspace output signal. Otherwise, exit Fast Restart mode and start a new simulation.</entry>
    <entry key="FromWksBlkDescr"><![CDATA[
Read data values specified in timeseries, matrix, or structure format from the MATLAB workspace, model workspace, or mask workspace.\n\nMATLAB timeseries format may be used for any data type, complexity, or fixed dimensions. To load data for a bus signal, use a MATLAB structure that matches the bus hierarchy and specify timeseries for each leaf signal.\n\nFor matrix formats, each row of the matrix has a time stamp in the first column and a vector containing the corresponding data sample in the subsequent column(s).\n\nFor structure format, use the following kind of structure:\n
    var.time=[TimeValues]\n
    var.signals.values=[DataValues]\n
    var.signals.dimensions=[DimValues]\n
]]></entry>
   
    <!-- Root Inport Errors -->
    <entry key="MdlUTNotSupportedFormat">Input format not supported. Available formats include: (1) a Simulink.SimulationData.Dataset object, (2) a double non-complex matrix, (3) a structure with or without time, (4) a MATLAB timeseries object, (5) a structure with MATLAB timeseries objects at all leaves (for bus input). All formats require the data to be finite (not Inf or NaN).</entry>
    <entry key="MdlUTNonScalarDataset">A non-scalar Simulink.SimulationData.Dataset object used for external input. When using a Simulink.SimulationData.Dataset object for external input, even though it may contain multiple elements, the object itself must be a scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="MdlUTNotSupportedFormatWithDatasetRef">Input format not supported. Available formats include: (1) a Simulink.SimulationData.Dataset object, (2) a Simulink.SimulationData.DatasetRef object, (3) a double non-complex matrix, (4) a structure with or without time, (5) a MATLAB timeseries object, (6) a structure with MATLAB timeseries objects at all leaves (for bus input). All formats require the data to be finite (not Inf or NaN).</entry>
    <entry key="MdlUTNonScalarDatasetRef">A non-scalar Simulink.SimulationData.DatasetRef object used for external input. When using a Simulink.SimulationData.DatasetRef object for external input, even though it may reference a Dataset with multiple elements, the object itself must be a scalar.</entry>
    <entry key="MdlUTSimulinkAndMatlabTimeseries">Model input cannot combine Simulink.Timeseries or Simulink.TsArray formats with MATLAB timeseries formats (including structure of MATLAB timeseries).</entry>
    <entry key="TimeseriesUnsupportedDataType">Invalid variable ''{0}'' specified as {1} input in ''{2}''. The input is either a timeseries or a Dataset with elements containing timeseries. The Data property of timeseries must be a built-in numeric, logical, fixed point or enumerated type. Data must be finite (not Inf or NaN).</entry>
    <entry key="TimeseriesUnsupportedIsTimeFirst">The timeseries variable ''{0}'' specified as {1} input in ''{2}'' cannot be loaded.  For this timeseries, the combination of the IsTimeFirst property and the dimensionality of the Data property is not supported. To load data for this input, update the dimension of the Data property of the timeseries object:\n
      -If the signal is a scalar or a 1-D vector, time must be the first dimension.\n
      -If the signal has more than 1 dimension, time must be the last dimension.
    </entry>
    <entry key="SimTimeseriesUnsupportedDataType">Invalid Simulink.Timeseries variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}''. The Data property must be a built-in numeric, logical, fixed point or enumerated type. The dimensions of the Data property must be non-zero.</entry>
    <entry key="InportDiscSampleTime">Invalid sample time for root level port ''{0}''. Since the external input corresponding to the inport does not specify any time values, the sample time must be discrete.</entry>           
    <entry key="InportInvalidMatrixDataLoading">Invalid matrix variable entered in the ''Input'' field of the Data Import/Export page of the Configuration Parameters dialog of model {0}. For this model, the input variable must be a structure. Matrix input can only be used if all the signals connected to the root inports are real (non-complex), double vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="InportDataTypeMismatch"><![CDATA[Invalid data type for root level port ''{0}''. The model is configured to load its root level ports from the workspace.  These external inputs have data type ''{1}''.  This data type does not agree with the data type, ''{2}'', that is being set for this root level port.<actions exclusiveFixIts="yes"><action cmd="matlab:" type="suggestion">Change the data type of the input data to type ''{3}''</action><action cmd="matlab:slprivate(''simulinkfixes'',''InportDataTypeMismatch'',''{0}'')" type="fixit">Turn off loading of external inputs by going to the Simulation menu and selecting Configuration Parameters. On the Data Import/Export page, locate the Load from workspace group and uncheck the Input checkbox</action></actions>]]></entry>
    <entry key="InportDataTypeMismatchFix">Executed the command 'set_param(model, 'LoadExternalInput', 'off')'</entry>           
    <entry key="FcnCallInportDataTypeMismatch">Invalid workspace data format for
    root Inport ''{0}''. The model is configured to load its root level ports
    from the workspace. This root Inport is configured to output a
    function call. Use one of these approaches: a) For the workspace data to be
    loaded, use a column vector of monotonically non-decreasing time values; b) For
    this root Inport, clear the ''Output function call'' block parameter; or c)
    Turn off loading of external inputs by clearing the Configuration Parameters
    -> Data Import/Export -> Input parameter.</entry>
    <entry key="NonFcnCallInportDataTypeMismatch">Invalid workspace data format
    for root Inport ''{0}''. The model is configured to load its root level
    ports from the workspace. The workspace data specified for this root Inport
    is a column vector; you should use that format only with a root Inport that
    outputs a function-call signal. Use one of these approaches: a) For the
    workspace data to be loaded, use a format other than a column vector; b) For
    this root Inport, select the ''Output function call'' block parameter; or c)
    Turn off loading of external inputs by clearing the Configuration Parameters
    -> Data Import/Export -> Input parameter.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidTsForFcnCallInportWithSpecifiedTs">Invalid workspace data for root-level Inport ''{0}''. Because the Inport is configured to output a function call with a discrete sample time of {1}, the time vector must be empty if any of the function-call subsystems it drives are configured to execute periodically. Consider using one of these approaches: \n\t1) For the workspace data to be loaded, use an empty vector []; \n\t2) Configure every function-call subsystem this Inport drives to a triggered function-call subsystem, by setting 'Sample time type' parameter of the Trigger Port block inside the function-call subsystem to 'triggered'; \n\t3) For this Inport, specify the ''Sample time' to inherited (-1); \n\t4) Turn off loading of external inputs by clearing the Configuration Parameters -> Data Import/Export -> Input parameter.</entry>
    <entry key="InportArrayNonDblDataType">Invalid data type for root level port ''{0}'' external data. The root level input port is set to use data type ''{1}'' but the external data is an array of type ''double''.  To load external data of non-double data type, change the external input to use structure format, timeseries format, or disable loading of external input.  Loading of external inputs is disabled by going to the Simulation menu and selecting Configuration Parameters.  On the Data Import/Export page, locate the Load from workspace group and uncheck the Input checkbox.</entry>
    <entry key="InportComplexityMismatch">Invalid signal type for port ''{0}''. Although the external inputs specified for the block diagram indicate that the data is complex, the port is set to be real.</entry>
    <entry key="InportDiscCannotInterp">Invalid setting for parameter ''Interpolate'' in ''{0}''. When time field is not specified in the workspace variable corresponding to a root level port, interpolation must be turned off.</entry>
    <entry key="InportDataMustBeFinite">The root level port ''{0}'' is configured to load data from variable ''{1}'' that contains Inf or Nan. Data must be finite (not Inf or NaN).</entry>
    <entry key="InportCannotInterpFiOrEnum">The root level port ''{0}'' is configured to load data from variable ''{1}'' that contains fi or enumeration data. Interpolation must be turned off.</entry>
    <entry key="InportInvalidSpecifiedFcnCallTime">Root level port ''{0}'' is configured to load data from a variable that contains function-call time data. The difference between the time value ({1}) specified by this variable and the offset ({3}) specified on the port is not an integer multiple of the step size ({2}) specified on the port.</entry>
    <entry key="InportInvalidSpecifiedFcnCallTimeNoOffset">Root level port ''{0}'' is configured to load data from a variable that contains function-call time data. The time value ({1}) specified by this variable is not an integer multiple of the step size ({2}) specified on the port.</entry>
    <entry key="InportInvalidFcnCallTime">Root level port ''{0}'' is configured to load data from a variable that contains function-call time data. The time value ({1}) specified by this variable is not an integer multiple of the fixed step size ({2}) of the model.</entry>
    <entry key="InportPortDimsMismatch">Invalid port dimensions for port ''{0}''. The external inputs specified for the block diagram indicate that the port dimensions should be {1}. Instead, the port dimensions are being set to {2}.</entry>
    <entry key="InportPortDimsMismatchAOB">The dimensions {1} of input data {3} are inconsistent with the dimensions {2} of port ''{0}''. The number of input dimensions must be smaller than or equal to the number of port dimensions, and each dimension of input data must be smaller than or equal to the corresponding port dimension.</entry>
    <entry key="InportPortDimsMismatchAOBForHier">The dimensions {1} of input data {3} for port ''{0}'' are inconsistent with the dimensions {2} of bus object {4}. The number of input dimensions must be smaller than or equal to the number of bus object dimensions, and each dimension of input data must be smaller than or equal to the corresponding bus object dimension.</entry>
    <entry key="InportNonScalarTimeseries">The external input data for model ''{0}'' is of type Simulink.SimulationData.Dataset. The input data element {1} for port ''{2}'' is a non-scalar timeseries array. Rapid Accelerator supports external input from timeseries objects within a Simulink.SimulationData.Dataset instance only if it is a scalar timeseries object.</entry>
    <entry key="RootInportDimsModeMismatch1">The parameter ''Variable size signal'' for ''{0}'' is set to ''No''. However, the workspace data corresponding to this root level port contains a variable-size signal. Change the parameter ''Variable size signal'' to ''Yes''.</entry>
    <entry key="RootInportDimsModeMismatch2">The parameter ''Variable size signal'' for ''{0}'' is set to ''Yes''. However, the workspace data corresponding to this root Inport contains a fixed-size signal. Change the parameter ''Variable size signal'' to ''No''.</entry>
    <entry key="RootInportNonVirtBusDimsModeMismatch">The Bus Object specified on ''{0}'' contains a variable-size Bus element. However, the workspace data corresponding to this root Inport does not have the ''valueDimensions'' field for the Bus element. Fix the Bus Object ''DimensionsMode'' field to match the workspace data.</entry>
    <entry key="FrmWksNonVirtBusDimsModeMismatch">The bus object specified on ''{0}'' contains a variable-size bus element. From Workspace blocks do not support loading data for variable-sized bus elements.</entry>

    <entry key="BlockDataValuesType">The variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}'' contains an unsupported Values property.  The Values property must be a scalar timeseries or MATLAB structure with timeseries at the leaves.</entry>

    <entry key="DatasetEmpty">The variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}'' contains a Dataset with no elements.
    Use the addElement method to add elements to this dataset for loading.</entry>
    <entry key="DatasetNestedElements">The Dataset variable specified as {0} input in ''{1}'' contains a nested Dataset
    at element {2,number,integer}.  To use Dataset objects to load external inputs, create a flat list of elements
    using the addElement method.</entry>
    
    <entry key="MultipleDatasets">Multiple external inputs are using Dataset objects. To load external
    input data using a Simulink.SimulationData.Dataset object, you must add all inputs to a single Dataset.</entry>
    <entry key="MultipleDatasetRefs">Multiple external inputs are using DatasetRef objects. To load external
    input data using a Simulink.SimulationData.DatasetRef object, you must have all inputs in a single DatasetRef object.</entry>
    <entry key="ExtraTriggerData">The model ''{0}'' specifies external input data for a trigger port but does not contain
    any root-level trigger ports. </entry>
    <entry key="ExtraEnableData">The model ''{0}'' specifies external input data for a enable port but does not contain
    any root-level enable ports. </entry>
    <entry key="InportNonDoubleTimeValues">The time values of input data {0} for port ''{1}'' are not of type double. For loading data using timeseries objects, the time values must be of type double.</entry>
    <entry key="DatasetExtInputInvalidElementContents">The external input data for model ''{0}'' is of type Simulink.SimulationData.Dataset. Simulink supports external input of this type only if each of the dataset elements is one of the following: a double real matrix of kind [time data] containing a sequence of non-decreasing values in the first column, a double real column vector containing a sequence of non-decreasing values (used only for function call signal loading), a scalar timeseries object, a structure of scalar timeseries objects, or an object derived from Simulink.SimulationData.BlockData with the Values property being a scalar timeseries or a structure of scalar timeseries objects.</entry>
    <entry key="ExtInputSparseInvalidElementContents">The external input data
    for model ''{0}'' contains a sparse matrix. Simulink does not support sparse
    matrix data in external input. </entry>
    <!-- Bus Errors -->
    <entry key="InportDataNonBusDataForBus">The root level port ''{0}'' specifies a bus object, but the external input workspace variable ''{1}'' is not compatible with buses. To load external inputs for bus ports, use a structure containing MATLAB timeseries objects or modify the ''Input'' field of the Data Import/Export page of the Configuration Parameters dialog.</entry>
    <entry key="FrmWksDataNonBusDataForBus">The From Workspace block ''{0}'' specifies a bus object, but the workspace variable ''{1}'' is not compatible with buses. To load bus data with From Workspace blocks, use a structure containing MATLAB timeseries objects.</entry>
    <entry key="InportDataTypeNotBus">The root level port ''{0}'' is configured to load a TsArray object from the workspace but its data type ''{1}'' is not a Bus data type. Modify the ''Input'' field of the Data Import/Export page of the Configuration Parameters dialog.</entry>
    <entry key="InportStructDataTypeNotBus">The root level port ''{0}'' is configured to load a structure of timeseries objects from the workspace but its data type ''{1}'' is not a Bus data type. Modify the ''Input'' field of the Data Import/Export page of the Configuration Parameters dialog.</entry>
    <entry key="FrmWksStructDataTypeNotBus">The From Workspace block ''{0}'' is configured to load a structure of timeseries objects from the workspace, but its data type ''{1}'' is not a bus data type. To load bus data in a From Workspace block, set the "Output data type" to ''Bus: BusObjectName''.</entry>
    <entry key="InportBusDataTypeMismatch">Invalid data type for root level inport ''{0}''. Element {1,number,integer} of the TsArray input object specified for this block indicates that the data type is ''{2}''. This data type does not agree with the data type ''{3}'' that is being set by the BusObject. To find the appropriate element in the input TsArray, execute object.flatten in the MATLAB command window and index into the resulting cell array</entry>
    <entry key="InportBusComplexityMismatch">Invalid signal type for inport ''{0}''. Element {1,number,integer} of the TsArray input object specified for this block indicates that the data should be complex. Instead, the corresponding element in the BusObject is set to real. To find the appropriate element in the input TsArray, execute object.flatten in the MATLAB command window and index into the resulting cell array.</entry>
    <entry key="InportBusDimsMismatch">Invalid port dimensions for inport ''{0}''. Element {1,number,integer} of the TsArray input object specified for this block indicates that the dimensions should be {2}. Instead, the element dimensions is specified to be {3} by the BusObject. To find the appropriate element in the input TsArray, execute object.flatten in the MATLAB command window and index into the resulting cell array.</entry>
    <entry key="FromWksArrayOfSubBus">The From Workspace block ''{0}'' specifies a bus object containing a nonscalar sub-bus. Loading external data for arrays of buses is not supported.  To avoid this error, use a separate From Workspace block for each scalar bus and use a Vector Concatenate block.</entry>
    <entry key="FromWksNotSupportArrayOfBus">The input data {1} for From Workspace block ''{0}'' contains a nonscalar structure. The From Workspace block does not support loading data for arrays of buses.</entry>
    <entry key="InportBusStructDataTypeMismatch">Inconsistent data type for {0} input to ''{1}''. Field ''{2}'' of the input structure specified for this block indicates that the data type is ''{3}''. This data type does not agree with the data type ''{4}'' that is being set by the bus object.</entry>
    <entry key="InportBusStructComplexityMismatch">Inconsistent signal type for {0} input to ''{1}''. Field ''{2}'' of the input structure specified for this block indicates that the data is complex. The corresponding element in the bus object is set to real.</entry>
    <entry key="InportBusStructDimsMismatch">Inconsistent port dimensions for {0} input to ''{1}''. Field ''{2}'' of the input structure specified for this block indicates that the dimensions are {3}. The element dimensions are set to {4} by the bus object.</entry>
    <entry key="InportDataTSAndBusTypeDoNotMatch">The bus data type specified by the root level inport ''{0}'' does not match the TsArray object in the workspace. The TsArray object must contain the same number of TimeSeries elements as specified by the BusObject.</entry>
    <entry key="InportDataHierStructForNonBus">The bus data type specified by the root level inport ''{0}'' does not match the structure of the input variable in the workspace. Field ''{1}'' of the structure must be a timeseries object.</entry>
    <entry key="FrmWksDataHierStructForNonBus">The bus data type specified by the From Workspace block ''{0}'' does not match the structure of the input variable in the workspace. Field ''{1}'' of the structure must be a timeseries object.</entry>
    <entry key="InportDataHierStructLeafForBus">The bus data type specified by the root level inport ''{0}'' does not match the structure of the input variable in the workspace. Field ''{1}'' of the structure is a timeseries object but the bus object indicates this bus element is a bus.</entry>
    <entry key="FrmWksDataHierStructLeafForBus">The bus data type specified by the From Workspace block ''{0}'' does not match the structure of the input variable in the workspace. Field ''{1}'' of the structure is a timeseries object but the bus object indicates this bus element is a bus.</entry>
    <entry key="InportDataEmptyHierStructForBus">The external input specified for root inport ''{0}'' contains bus data with no fields.  To use ground values for this input port, change the variable ''{1}'' to an empty MATLAB array (i.e. "[]").</entry>
    <entry key="FrmWksDataEmptyHierStructForBus">The workspace data specified for From Workspace block ''{0}'' contains bus data with no fields. To load bus data, at least 1 field must be specified.</entry>
    <entry key="InportDataHierStructExtraField">The Bus data type specified by the root level inport ''{0}'' does not match the structure of the input variable in the workspace. Field ''{1}'' of the structure is not an element of the bus.</entry>
    <entry key="FrmWksDataHierStructExtraField">The Bus data type specified by the From Workspace block ''{0}'' does not match the structure of the input variable in the workspace. Field ''{1}'' of the structure is not an element of the bus.</entry>

    <!-- Utility Function Errors -->
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructTsArrayArg">To construct a hierarchy from a Simulink.TsArray object, only 1 argument is permitted.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructBusObjArg">To construct a MATLAB structure from a bus object, the first argument must be the name of a bus object. The optional second argument can be either a cell array of MATLAB timeseries objects, or a structure of timeseries objects. If you specify a cell array of timeseries objects, you can use a third argument that specifies the dimension of the resulting structure. If you specify a structure of timeseries objects, that structure must have the same hierarchy as the bus object. However, the names of the fields in the structure of timeseries can be different from the nodes defined in the bus object.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructArg">The first argument must be a Simulink.TsArray object or the name of a valid Simulink.Bus object from the base workspace.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructBusObj">Unable to determine bus hierarchy. Verify the first argument is a name of a valid bus object in the base workspace.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructDataNumData">Invalid argument for structure timeseries initialization. The number of leaf elements in the first and second arguments do not match.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateBusSignalName">Simulink.TsArray contains field ''{0}'' that is not a MATLAB-valid identifier. Structure format requires all bus signals to use valid MATLAB identifiers.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructDataElement">Invalid argument for structure timeseries initialization. Cell array must contain only MATLAB timeseries or Simulink.Timeseries objects.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructDataType">Invalid argument for structure timeseries initialization.  Element {0,number,integer} is of type {1} but the bus object requires type {2}.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructFiMismatch">Invalid argument for structure timeseries initialization.  Element {0,number,integer} is a fixed point type but does not match Bus object fixed point settings.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructDataComplexity">Invalid argument for structure timeseries initialization.  Element {0,number,integer} is complex but the bus object requires real data.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidCreateStructDataDims">Invalid argument for structure timeseries initialization.  Element {0,number,integer} contains ''Data'' of dimension {1} but the bus object requires dimension {2}.</entry>
    <entry key="ConvertTimeseriesFrames">Simulink.Timeseries cannot be converted to MATLAB timeseries because this Timeseries contains frames.</entry>
    <entry key='InvalidCreateStructFromStruct'>To construct a MATLAB structure from a bus object, if the second argument is a structure of MATLAB timeseries objects, then the structure of timeseries must have the same hierarchy as the bus object. However, the names of the fields in the structure of timeseries can be different from the nodes defined in the bus object.</entry>

    <!-- Legacy Format Phase-out Errors -->
    <entry key="InportLegacyFormatLoading">The input data ''{1}'' for model ''{0}'' is of a format that is no longer supported.  Please use MATLAB timeseries in place of Simulink.Timeseries and structures of MATLAB timeseries objects in place of Simulink.TsArray.</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
